HERE!
Hmm...
Is it this way?
I didn't know we had a place like this.
IS Academy is really big.
TARGET CONFIRMED
AT LOCATION C.
ACCORDING TO PLAN,
HE'S HEADING OVER THERE.
ROGER THAT.
WE ARE STANDING BY.
Uh... So is it here?
Yamada-sensei!
I've got the materials
that you asked for.
Is this the wrong room?
Who are you?
What are you doing here?!
"LOVELY STYLE"
What's going on?
MAIDEN
BATTLE
START
Welcome to the forbidden fantasy land,
Orimura Ichika-kun.
Who are you?
CATER-TO-ICHIKA-ORIMURA
SERVICE BATTLE
Now it's finally begun!
This is the "Servicing Orimura Ichika showdown."
and I'm your presenter, Maya Yamada!
Yamada-sensei?!
Each of you chooses what you want to do,
and whoever captivates
Orimura-kun the most wins!
Alright, now, without anymore delay!
Please w-wait a minute! What is this exactly?!
This is... a secret competition!
Huh?
First, Entry #1!
Please welcome Houki Shinonono!
H-Houki?
Stop staring at me like that...
Okay, but...
I-Ichika, come onto stage!
L-let me serve you!
Houki... What's up with that costume?
I'm, dressed as a fox priestess.
Now I've got this urge to touch them.
S-stop staring at them so much.
S-sorry.
Do you want to drink some tea?
S-sure.
It's tasty.
Really? Do you want more?
Yeah, thanks.
Hot!
Sorry!
Are you okay?
That was... nothing.
I'm sorry.
I'm nervous, you know?
This is the first time I've dressed up like this,
so it's kind of embarrassing.
Did you get burnt?
N-no...
Time is up!
What?! That was too fast!
I'm sorry, but we have other people
going after you, so...
I'm sorry about that.
Don't worry. It's fine
now. It wasn't that hot.
More importantly...
May I touch them?
What?!
Just a little longer!
Let go of me!
What...?
C-Cecilia?!
Ichika-san, now it's time I
entertain you with my service.
Hey, what is this exactly?
I can't tell you that just yet.
Ichika, I'd like you to play billiards.
Billiards? I've never done this before.
Then I'll teach you how to play.
First, hold the cue like this...
Knock the balls into the
pockets, starting with
the smallest number on the table.
You're pretty good.
I'm not that good.
Oops!
It's your turn, Ichika.
So I'm supposed to put
that ball in the pocket, right?
Ichika, you need to loosen up a little.
Relax your shoulders and
hold your arm like this...
Cecilia, they're touching me...
Ichika, you need to concentrate.
I-I can't concentrate.
Don't worry. Just do what I say...
That's inappropriate!
Shinonono-san, don't stand up.
It's dangerous.
All right! Time's up!
Impressive as always, Ichika-san!
It's all thanks to your teaching Cecilia!
Let's do this again sometime!
Sure! Next time it'll
be just the two of us.
Oh?
Oww...
It's too early to turn on the lights!
Elevator...?
What?
Are you having fun, Ichika?
Charl, you, too?
What are you supposed to be?!
A french poodle.
I baked some cookies for you.
Thank you!
Hey, they look good! I
was just getting hungry.
Let me feed you, Ichika.
Close your eyes and open your mouth.
What?
L-like this?
Ichika, by any chance...
do you prefer it like this?
Wh-Wha-What!
Dunois-san, your turn is over!
That is totally inappropriate!
What?!
That idiot is just staring at her boobs!
Hey!
What?!
Will you zip this up for
me? I can't reach it.
Oh, sure.
Your ears are crooked too.
All right, the equipment's
perfect! Moving out!
What now?!
Huh?
Now the "black bunny squad"
will demonstrate!
DREAM
Laura... I mean, what is this set?
Ichika, let's play a game of darts!
Sure. I've played this before.
Did you know?
There are also fantastic prizes!
Everybody gets something.
COUPON
One week's worth of coupons for the
daily lunch combos at the cafeteria.
Wow, that's wonderful!
All right, I'll do my best then.
Yes!
LAURA
What's this?
That's...
LAURA
...my swimsuit!
What's going on?
Due to budget constraints,
some of the prizes
are actually Bodewig-san's personal possessions.
What?
I-if you really want it..
W-What? I know I still
have some time left!
Ichika-kun!
This way, this way.
What? Wait...
Nyaa! Hi there.
Tatenashi-san, you as well!?
Hogging all the cute girls
all to yourself, huh?
That must really stroke your ego, Ichika-kun.
P-please stop that!
Hey, there's someone that I want to
introduce you at some point.
What?
She doesn't say much,
but she is a very cute girl.
Please just get off me.
Please, Ichika-kun. I'm being serious.
Tatenashi-san?
Come on! Things were going pretty well.
Rin?!
Give my costume back!
Sorry, Rin-chan. It looked fun
so I wanted to join you guys.
But your chest area,
it seems a little tight.
You...!
Anyway calm down, Rin!
Shut up!
First of all, I wouldn't
have let my guard down
if you weren't staring at her boobs!
What are you talking about?
Admit it, Ichika-kun. You
were staring at them.
Sounds like you want
to be a dartboard.
Wait, wait! Let's talk about this!
Well, lets continue this later, Ichika!
Everyone, please come back to the stage.
We still have one more event left.
What?
I thought all of us
already had a turn...
What?!
Chifuyu-nee...?
Don't say a word. If
you do, I'll kill you.
Okay...
Open your mouth.
CATER-TO-ICHIKA-ORIMURA
SERVICE BATTLE
BIRTHDAY PARTY
FOR ICHIKA ORIMURA
Now that I think about it, today is...
Happy birthday, Ichika!
You know, you really didn't need to
do all that just for my birthday.
You tend to forget your
birthday every year.
So we decided to surprise you!
We also wanted to make it memorable.
It's not the amount of birthdays that matters.
This is an important birthday.
The outfits were my idea.
A certain German officer told me that
this is first-class treatment.
I see. Thank you, everyone.
Well, I'm glad you enjoyed it.
It was a little embarrassing, but we all
worked hard for it, so it was great.
I agree.
You were really wonderful Orimura-sensei.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yamada-sensei, thank you
for everything today.
You, as well, Chifuyu-nee.
At any rate, I can't believe
you actually dressed up like that.
You know, it's been a while since
I spent my birthday with you.
Not since I was a little kid, I guess.
Yeah, you're right.
What? What did you just say?
No, nothing!
By the way, Orimura,
who did the best today?
What?
Well...
Umm...
I'd say Chifuyu-nee!
What? Huh?
Ichika... You're the
worst kind of idiot!
Ichika!
That hurt... Why were they so mad?
But it was fun.
Who are you?
Chifuyu-nee?
No.
I am you, Ichika Orimura.
What?
You did fight me last time.
Are you the one who pilots Silent Zephyrus?!
That's right.
My name is Madoka Orimura.
In order for me to continue being myself,
I must take your life!
Another beautiful day!
It dries the clothes so nicely!
For me, Charlotte Dunois,
the day starts with
making an omelet for my beloved Ichika!
Oriumra-Sensei?!
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
"The Secret Base"