Ichika-kun!
Huh? What's wrong, Ichika-kun?
Are you seriously asking me, "What's wrong?"
Seriously! Please, just put some clothes on!
What? I am wearing clothes.
Put some pants on!
It won't open.
Come on!
Quit being such a baby, and  you have a good reputation for massages.
So give me a massage
What?
It would help me feel ready for tomorrow's school festival.
Come on. Please?
As a man, it'd be horrible for me to massage that body.
It's definitely a horrible idea!
If you keep giving me this much trouble, I'm going to have to force it open.
I'll make sure you don't!
If it won't open normally...
just break it open!
Hey...
Now, give me a massage! Give me a massage!
All right.
I'm sure we'll get to see each other again
kitto aeru yo
As we cherish the smiles and tears
egao to namida wo idaite
Together
kimi to issho ni
"What color will the sky be tomorrow?" I wonder
asu no sora wa naniiro ni kawaru kana
I'll light the world on my own
jibun no chikara de kagayakasete yukou
I don't know what'll happen
shiranai koto
But that's what makes it so exciting
dakara doki doki suru ne
I want to keep trying new things
tameshitai motto
No need to limit ourselves
genkai wa kimenakute ii
Listen to what the wind is trying to tell us
kizuite kaze no koe ga oshieru
Let's move onward to our next story
susumou tsugi no monogatari e to
Once I take off, I'll never run away, even if I might lose
habataite makesou demo nigetari shinai
I'll believe in the time we've spent together
kimi to kizamu toki wo shinjite yukou
We'll reach the light
hikari made
As we cherish the smiles and tears
egao to namida wo idaite
To protect my dearest
taisetsu na hito mamoru tame ni
I'll grow stronger
tsuyoku nare
Translucent Chord of Cinderella's Heel
Welcome!
This way, please, ojou-sama.
No way! You get to have Orimura-kun wait on you here?
Not only that, but he's wearing a swallow-tailed coat!
You get to take pictures with him, too!
Just the two of you! Just the two of you!
Hey, you butler over there!
Why won't you take me to my table?
What?
What are you wearing?
Shut up! We're doing a Chinese cafe in Class 2.
Hey, your hairstyle's different today.
Oh, this?
It's called a chignon.
Yeah, It looks as good as ever on you.
Well... This isn't too different from my usual apperance, so...
Just take me to my table already!
Yes, yes.
Well then, milady, right this way please.
Millady...
What would you like to order?
Well, let's see...
What is this "Reward For Your Butler" set?
Ojou-sama, would you prefer our most popular item, the cake set instead?
Hey, you're trying to pull a fast one on me, aren't you?
Not at all.
Then give me one "Reward For Your Butler" set.
Thank you for waiting, Milady.
O-Okay.
Wh-Why are we sitting together?
Well, I don't particularly mind.
A-Anyway what kind of set is this?
Y-You get to feed me.
Huh?
Essentially, with this set, you get to feed your butler.
Wh-What kind of set is that?
The customer has to feed you sweets?
That's why I didn't want you to pick it.
You don't have to do it if you don't want to.
I mean...
But it's already here .
So I might as well...
reward you with some sweets!
Okay!
Say, "ah!"
Ah...
I-I fed you, so feed me now...
Milady, I apologize, but I'm afraid that's not a part of our services.
Rin.
You're kind of cute.
Hey, are you okay?
Wh-Where the hell did that come from?!
The way you eat is so...
I-It's... cute?
Yeah.
You're like a  squirrel.
What's with her?
Reiko Makigami
May I have a word with you please?
I do.
Um... So you're Makigami Reiko-san?
Yes. I was wondering if you would use my company's equipment on your Byakushiki.
Well, I don't really know  much about equipment.
Come on. Don't be like that.
How about this additional armor or this auxiliary thruster?
Act right now, and we'll throw in another leg blade, too.
Well, Really I'm fine as is...
My deepest apologies, ma'am, but the next customer is waiting for him.
I'm sorry, Please excuse me.
Thank you, Takatsuki-san. You're a lifesaver.
Lately, people have been trying to persuade me to put  different equipment  on my Byakushiki.
Don't worry about it.
I guess you've been through a lot lately.
You can go ahead and take a break.
Why don't you take a look around the school?
Are you sure?
Let's see... You have about half an hour.
If you say so.
Well, Ichika-san, I'll accompany you.
Hey! That's not fair, Cecilia!
Wait! If that's the case... Me too!
All right. Let's go, Ichika.
Hey, you guys can't just leave the store unattended like that!
Why don't you settle it with rock-paper-scissors?
Rock-paper-scissors!
Brass Ensemble Exhibition
Wow, I managed to play a note!
Yeah. You're pretty good, Orimura-kun.
Why don't you join our club?
No, I don't think I'd be able....
What about Cecilia?
M-Me? I've never played a wind instrument before.
Is that so?
You look like you could play the flute or something...
just like a well raised girl would.
A well raised girl?
Come on. Give it a try.
But this is...
a-an indirect kiss...
What was that?
Nothing!
Nothing at all!
W-Well, here I go.
I'll swap out another mouthpiece for you.
Well, I'd better get back to work.
Elusive
Ta-da!
T-Tatenashi-san?!
Elusive
Ichika-kun, I want you to help us with the student council's performance of
an action-packed interactive play!
Anyways come with me!
What?
Yup, it's settled!
Wait a sec...
Just change into these, and come to the stage.
What?
And this... is very important.
The crown!
Um, I haven't even taken a look at the script.
Don't worry about that!
This play is  basically all improvised anyway.
We'll give you all the directions necessary.
I'll leave things up to you. Okay, Ichika?
Now, let's get this started!
Once upon a time, there was a girl named Cinderella.
What? What?
No... It's no longer a name.
Those who gleefully brought down
swarms of enemy soldiers across countless balls...
The most powerful warriors in the world...
Those who revel in utter destruction...
What?
Together, those girls held the fitting title of...
Cinderella!
What?!
The girls dance around, targeting the confidential data...
hidden inside the Prince's crown!
Cinderella
What?
And tonight, the time of the bloodthirsty Cinderellas has come once again.
That's mine!
Give me that crown!
What would you do if those actually hit me?!
Don't worry. All of the weapons are harmless props.
I doubt that!
H-Hey, your panties!
You're wearing glass slippers?!
Don't worry. They're made from tempered glass.
Are you crazy? This is dangerous!
You wait!
A sniper rifle? Does that mean it's Cecilia?
What the hell is wrong with this play?!
He got away.
I think I'll give away the right to live with Ichika-kun
to whoever manages to get the crown he's wearing.
I don't know if you're allowed to do that.
Don't worry.
I'll make it happen with my authority as student council president.
I swear, I will win this no matter what!
You're mine now.
Ichika, this way!
Char...
Char... You saved me!
I'm sure they're right behind you, so go ahead and run!
Thanks!
Oh, just wait.
What is it?
Well, it would make me happy if you could give me the crown..
Oh, sure. I don't see why not.
For the prince, his country means everything.
So if he ever loses his crown, which contains the confidential data...
What?
He gets electrically shocked due to his own remorse!
Oh, bless his heart!
Ichika!
Is the prince's dedication to his country that unwaivering?
But all we can do is watch over him. How agonizing!
All right, all right. I get it already.
So you heard, right?
Sorry, I can't give you the crown, Char.
What? That's a problem!
This is it for you!
Be a good boy, and hold still!
End of the line!
Watch out!
Jeez!
Get away from him!
Ichika? Where are you?
It's dark.
It's the end.
Where am I?
Did I die?
What's this? It's soft.
I-Ichika! I didn't realize you were there.
O-Oh yeah! I'd better keep running!
What? Wait up!
This should be far enough.
What?
I've been waiting for you.
Your crown is mine.
Whoa!
That's dangerous!
You're my bride, so give it up already!
Suspension Bridge Effect
Love is no fun without obstacles!
Laura!
This is rather dangerous.
Let's go, Laura!
Ichika...
Well then.
Ichika!
Ichika, this way!
Houki?!
Climb this to safety.
Ichika, don't  look up.
What?
D-Don't look!
Stop it! You're going to make me fall!
I made it.
Well then, give me the crown.
What?
Don't be so naive, silly girl!
Oh, no!
Let's get out of here, Houki!
This is bad!  Really bad!
Over there!
We're safe.
C-Could you please let me go?
Oops, sorry.
In general why does everyone want this?
That's because...
Well, uh...
The crown is mine!
In your dreams!
What do you think you're doing?
Get out of my way, Laura!
My sentiments exactly!
Hey, stop it, you guys!
I'm going to take care of you first.
Go ahead and try!
Excuse me...
You saw, didn't you?
Get your hands off my bride!
What?
The contestants from the free group are now welcome to participate
Good luck in getting the prince's crown!
Hold still, Orimura-kun!
Let us be off and live happily ever after, my prince!
Give me that crown!
Orimu, wait up...
They won't find you here.
Thanks.
Wait, why are you here, Makigami-san?
Well,
I thought I should use this opportunity to take your Byakushiki.
What?
Just give it to me already!
Who are you?
Me?
I'm the mysterious lady, disguised as someone
from a corporate business.
Aren't you happy?
Byakushiki!
I've been waiting for you to use that!
Look up high into the beautiful sky
takaku motto beautiful sky
With a steady gaze
sukitooru manazashi de
I want to protect that radiance
mamoritai kagayaki ga kyou mo
It keeps me going
chikara ni naru yo
I can feel you in the wind
naranda kaze ni kimi wo kanjiru
I'm so glad that you're there
sonzai ga ureshii
When I take a deep breath and look up into the sky
shinkokyuu shite miageru sora wa
It looks different every time
mainichi chigau kao nan da
We can go anywhere
doko made mo ikeru ne
If we take it step by step from here
egaiteku koko kara
I want to be stronger than I was the day before
kinou yori tsuyoi jibun de itai
Every day
itsu demo
Look up high into the beautiful sky
takaku motto beautiful sky
With a steady gaze
sukitooru manazashi ni
Let's commit this moment to our memories
kono shunkan wo yakitsukete iku
We'll make the beautiful sky even brighter
hikare motto beautiful sky
I'll embrace you and your wings
tsubasa goto dakishimete
I want to protect that radiance
mamoritai kagayaki ga kyou mo
It's what keeps me going
chikara wo kureru
Preview
Good day, everyone!
I, Cecilia Alcott, have formed a new faction, in an effort to make
your life at IS Academy even better!
So, please vote for Cecilia Alcott, everyone!
Vote for Cecilia Alcott!
What? Orimura-sensei?!
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2, "The Mysterious Lady"!
The Mysterious Lady