Who are you?
My name is Madoka Orimura.
I'm here to take your life.
I wonder when you'll die.
Laura!
You bitch! You think taking my bride's hand is alright?
Silent Zephyrus!
What a pain.
Did she get away?
Are you okay, Laura?
I should be the one asking you that.
Do you know why she was after you?
No, I don't know.
What's the matter?
You have beautiful eyes...
What?
They look like precious gemstones...
You were just attacked! Why are you so relaxed?
Usually I don't get to see them, so...
Beautiful... Ichika said
that I look beautiful...
Anyway, you showed up
at just the right time.
Well, that's because I was looking for
a chance to be alone with you.
I can't believe you
just made me say that!
What was that for?
The Secret Base
So, we're escorting IS equipment?
Yeah. Supposedly we were asked to test
prototype equipment from different counties.
But...
Sorry I have to help out around the house.
There's this meeting that I must attend.
Actually I'm assigned
to a different duty.
Clarissa, about the
stuff we talked about...
Everyone seems busy.
Well, I guess I'll do it alone.
You didn't have to come, Ichika.
You were just attacked the other day.
Which is why I can't be calm if you doing this alone.
I'll be fine.
Oh boy...
What was that?
I'll go check it out!
Wait, Ichika!
Who are they?
They have no nationality or ID code!
Let's go, Charl!
Okay, Ichika!
They're fast.
Just let us catch you,
so you don't get hurt.
IS pilots?
Doesn't matter.
Get rid of them!
Damn!
You're pretty good.
I won't let you get away!
You're making my Revive cry
with your poor handling!
Shut up!
Ichika!
Give up already. You can't defeat us.
Charl!
Are you okay, Ichika-san?
I'm okay.
Could you be any slower?
You should never let
your guard down, Ichika.
I'm sorry that I made you guys worry.
My god! What should we do with you?
Really now.
I'm sorry.
I don't see any problem
with Orimura's body,
but I detected some abnormalities
in Byakushiki's quantum shift function.
Orimura-kun?
Yes.
Draw sword: Yukihira!
He's unable to deploy his equipment.
What's the cause?
I can't say without further tests.
Orimura, hand over your Byakushiki.
But we don't know when
Phantom Task might show up.
That's the plan.
What are you going to do if you can't deploy Byakushiki?
But...
You'd be better if you didn't have that defective power.
Or do you feel scared
without Byakushiki?
I'm not scared, Chifuyu-nee.
That's good to know.
Now the problem is...
"what if the girls find out about it"?
I know they're going to panic,
but from a security
perspective it is essential
to at least inform the candidates.
This is giving me a headache...
Please don't inform them. I'll protect Ichika!
I must protect Ichika...
Ichika, which one do you like?
Striped is Best!
What is this?
Hey, Laura!
Why are you suddenly showing him that?
Close your eyes, Ichika.
I'm only trying to find
out my bride's tastes.
"Your bride's tastes"?
Yeah, Clarissa told me...
When a girl is in love,
something called the "panty
flash event" arises occasionally.
It's when a boy accidentally
catches a glimpse of her panties.
In this situation captain, you must always
wear panties that
you wouldn't mind showing
to Ichika Orimura!
And these striped panties
are
the absolute best at improving a man's impression of you!
The absolute best...
The design isn't bad.
Right. I have the same kind myself.
Chelsea, I want to order new underwear.
I want the design to have
horizontal stripes...
No, no, no, it's not like that at all.
Is he flustered because it's true?
My bride is so modest.
That's not it!
What kind of underwear
do you think is best, Charlotte?
Laura, you're not supposed to talk about
stuff like that in front of a boy.
I'm sorry, but I have to go.
No way...
What just happened to
my underwear all of a sudden?
...detected some abnormalities
in Byakushiki's quantum shift...
...therefore he's unable
to deploy the equipment.
Don't tell me the same thing is
happening with my underwear, too?!
This time for sure...
Not again! What should I do?
Charl, are you in there?
I-Ichika?! What's wrong?
Class has already started.
What? Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry, Ichika.
What's wrong?
Well, uhh...
It's okay now...
Okay, then let's go!
Wait, Ichika!
Give me a second. Can you slow down?
What are you talking about?
You know it's my sister's class.
That's true, but...
Come on, sprint! Sprint!
Whoa, don't pull me like that!
My bad...
I'm okay!
No!
How long is this going to continue?
Hey, Houki.
Can I sit here?
Sure, go ahead.
What's wrong?
N-nothing.
The chair feels cold.
Here, Rin-san!
Okay, Charlotte!
Leave this to me.
Attack!
What?
The timing was slightly off.
Why do I have to do this
on a day like this?
Hey, Charl. I'll help you.
Charl, your rhythm is off today.
I'm sorry, Ichika...
The issues with Byakushiki
must have gotten you worried.
I'm sorry.
It's not like that at all.
Actually I'm glad I'm able
to help you, Ichika.
I'm grateful, but don't do anything unreasonable.
Okay.
You're so kind, Ichika.
Did you say something?
No, nothing in particular!
Hey!
C-Clarissa, it's me!
There's an emergency!
Charlotte Dunois has no underwear on?!
I may have opened Pandora's box...
Do you remember the "panty flash event"
we talked about?
Of course.
There are some cases where you can't see
the panties that are supposed to be there.
What did you say?
It's a special case, the so-called
"she-has-nothing-on" moment,
which occurs due to the angle,
the amount of light and
various other conditions.
The "She-has-nothing-on" moment?!
That means Charlotte was actually...
Most likely, you just couldn't see her panties.
I see...
So Charlotte was actually
wearing her panties.
Good. That's really good.
I expect nothing less from
the Black Bunny Squad Vice Captain!
She doesn't love Japanese anime
and manga for nothing!
That's why I admire her
and want to be like her!
Looks like I didn't have
to lose my war buddy.
War buddy...?
I'm a little jealous that
she makes you say that.
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Captain, we, the Black Bunny Squad,
are always with you.
Please don't ever forget that.
I appreciate that, Clarissa.
Thank you for helping me.
I'll inform the teacher, so you can go ahead
and head back to the classroom.
Okay. Don't do anything unreasonable.
Thank God that he didn't find out.
What happened to Byakushiki
also happened to my underwear...
I need to hurry and do something about this.
But that means I'll have to have
Revive inspected, too...
If that happens I won't
be able to protect Ichika.
That aside, if Ichika finds out
that I don't have any underwear on...
I had no idea you were
interested in things like that.
I'm more surprised than when
I found out that you were actually a girl.
It's not what you think!
Quite frankly, I'm shocked you're not wearing panties.
Listen, Ichika! I can explain!
I'm disappointed in you, Charl. Later...
Wait, Wait! Ichika!
That could happen... I don't want that!
Anyways I need to keep it  a secret  at least until
Ichika's Byakushiki returns to normal.
What a coincidence that I run into
you guys at a place like this.
I was moving some stuff to
the reference room for a teacher.
I-I'll see you later.
Hey, Charlotte.
About what you just said...
We need to know about it in more detail.
Why didn't you tell us that sooner?!
You shouldn't have hesitated!
Do you realize that
you're being targeted?
Did you guys figure
out about Byakushiki?
Then I have no choice
but to protect you.
No, it's time for me and
my Blue Tears to step in.
You're a sniper.
There's no way you can be his bodyguard.
Just leave it up to me and my Shenlong.
What did you say?
What!?
Hey, calm down!
Well...
Umm...!
Ichika, this way!
I'm sorry, Ichika.
You couldn't help what happened.
I'm really sorry.
Get down!
That's dangerous!
The output is reduced so don't worry.
Now you'll be under my protection.
Don't shoot lasers at the person
you're supposed to protect!
Get down!
It's Rin this time?
Don't worry. I just flicked it.
You threw that with all of your strength!
Allow me to protect you!
I'll do it!
I'm the one who will protect Ichika!
I'm not surrendering so easily!
I'll make it clear
who his true childhood friend is!
Umm, guys?
Okay, that's enough!
That's enough IS usage for
private matters inside the school!
You stay out of this!
This is our problem!
The outsider needs to step back!
I get it, I get it. Maybe I
should join you guys, too.
I'll get Ichika if I
defeat all of you, right?
THE ACADEMY'S STRONGEST
Thank goodness you guys are obedient.
I want the three of you
to rake the sand on the grounds.
What?
What kind of example would I be setting
if I didn't penalize you at all for
raising such a commotion?
Okay, thanks!
I feel guilty.
Yeah...
Well, I guess I'll go, too.
What? Where to?
To get yelled at by Chifuyu-nee.
This wouldn't have happened if it weren't
for Byakushiki to begin with.
Wait, then I should go...
But you worked hard, Charl.
Let me take the spotlight for a change.
But...
Thank you for everything today.
You made me happy.
Ichika is leaving because of me...
Ichika didn't do anything wrong...
Does this mean I should've told him
the truth much earlier?
That's impossible!
I won't be able to protect
Ichika if I told him that,
and he would hate me!
But
what should I do?
Why didn't you tell me about it?
Because I thought you
would get mad at me.
Are you hurt?
Aren't you mad at me?
Why would I be?
Because I broke your most cherished mirror.
There's nothing more precious
than you, Charlotte.
Mom...
I'm sorry!
The fact that you said
you are sorry is admirable.
Can you be honest from this point forward?
Yes, I won't tell a lie again, Mom!
That's right... He's not
going to hate me over this.
If I'm honest with him...
As long as I'm honest with him!
Wait!
There's something that
I need to tell you.
What is it all of a sudden?
Well, I...
H-hey, what do you think you're doing?
Please!
Charl?
Look... This is my...
...secret!
Charlotte.
What... What was I doing just now?
Hey, Laura, what's up?
Hmm...
Oh!
So you do wear underwear.
Of course I do!
Underwear?!
I do! Look, Ichika! Look!
You pervert, Ichika.
Why?!
Do you know the source of this?
I found out that one of the prototypes
we planned to import
had the ability to quantum
shift more effectively.
It must be the one that was destroyed
during the attack.
It went rampant
and that had some kind
of impact on Byakushiki.
Luckily, the impact was only temporary
and it's back to normal already.
What a troublemaker
we've got on our hands.
I'm glad Orimura is okay.
But his carelessness was the
cause of this to begin with.
He got what he deserved.
What?
Nothing in particular.
By the way, did you find out
who was behind the attack?
There's no connection with Phantom Task.
They were just spies sent by the corporation.
Only your underwear was forced
into quantum shift, huh?
What a day this has been.
Though,  having underwear that isn't recognizable as underwear
would probably be the best option.
Look.
Bloomers...
Why didn't I consider that?
Long ago, a princess in France said:
"If they don't have panties,
let them wear bloomers!"
No, she didn't!
It is a time of civil war.
We're in the great
civil war over Ichika.
We, the Black Bunny Squad,
may only have a small territory,
but our spirits are
higher than Mt. Fuji!
Now it's time for us to move out!
Instructor Orimura?!
"Sisters"
Next time on Infinite
Stratos 2, "Sisters"