It's still not good enough.
Still not good enough...
I bet my sister would be more...
If it weren't for Byakushiki,
I could've caught up to her...
No, that's not it...
Yo!
So, about the upcoming
tag-team tournament...
Would you to team up with me?
Kanzashi-san!
Stop calling out my name!
Sarashiki-san!
Don't call me by my last name, either!
Well, then...
You, girl over there!
What is your intention?
You just told me not
to call you by your name.
I'd rather be called by name
than be addressed that way.
Okay then. Kanzashi.
San...
What made you want to
team up with me anyway?
Uhh...
Please don't mention my name to her.
Oh, yeah!
Because I want to see your personal IS!
What...
Open Your Heart
Whoa! When did you get here?!
Don't tell me you're going
to ask Maintenance for help.
No, it's not for me.
I thought about asking them a favor
about Kanzashi's personal IS.
I think that would be a little difficult.
It looks like Kanazashi-chan's intention
to assemble it  herself.
What?
I did mine that way therefore
she's self-conscious about doing hers that way as well.
She shouldn't be worried about it.
So you assembled it yourself?
Yeah, I did.
Though I received some
advice from Kaoruko-chan and
the maintenance department.
More importantly, how has Kanzashi-chan been doing?
Well,
she hit me...
What? Normally she
wouldn't want to waste
energy on anything unproductive.
Did you touch her ass or something?
I wouldn't do that.
I'm joking, I'm joking.
But, Kanzashi-chan doing that.
I bet she has a crush on you, Ichika.
That's far enough!
What?
There's nothing to be afraid of!
Just leave it to me!
Take this!
I didn't expect to hit him... So why did I?
Ichika-san...
I'll make you regret
not teaming up with me.
Now shake to your core
as Cecilia Alcott
and Blue Tears play your requiem!
Hey, have you heard?
What is it?
Supposedly Orimura has been asking
Sarashiki-san from Class 4 every day
to be his partner in the
personal IS tag tournament!
What?! Liar! Why?
Like I said,
I need you to give me the package data
for my right side shock cannon now!
You need to finish it within three days.
What? You can't do it?
You'd better do it!
You watch, Ichika!
I won't forgive you even if you come
pleading for my forgiveness in tears!
Kanzashi-san, wait!
Stop following me!
Let's go, Revive!
I'm a formidable opponent, Ichika!
I'll show you true terror...
I'll engrave it into your heart, Ichika!
What if I tape it up...
What?
Medic! Medic!
The least I can do is show some mercy.
I'll kill you quickly so you won't suffer,
Ichika.
I got you, Houki!
What?! Tatenashi!
Oh? Using a real sword for training huh?
Yeah...
So, Houki, team up with me!
Huh?
First things first, let me
examine your physical data.
Okay, I don't mind.
All right, prepartions are complete! Let's get started.
This is...
Is something wrong?
You've got big boobs.
Mine might actually be beaten here.
Where are you looking?
Please get serious!
I'm sorry. My bad.
Since when did I start
feeling uncomfortable
about being a member of the
same Sarashiki family with her?
I can't even look at her face anymore...
If tomorrow's flight test goes well,
my sister will...
What's going on?
Advancing from a C to a S in
such a short period of time?
I've never heard of this.
As expected, the key is Tabane Shinonono...
I'd like to raise the booster output
in order to improve tuning performance.
That's fine, but it's
going to make controlling
the body difficult.
There will be a decrease in stability as well.
I don't care!
I can't afford to lose the
next battle, no matter what.
Hey!
Have you seen Kanzashi-san?
Get out of here!
That's right! We're going to report you!
What's making them so mad?
Will you get out of my way Orimura-kun?
What?
I see.
Due to the competition starting soon, everyone's become nervous.
I'd better hurry up, too.
Come, Uchigane Nishiki.
I'm going to make it work
today no matter what.
Body control is good.
And the hyper sensor
connection and interlock...
No problem with the attitude
control thrusters.
Adjusting deployment hardpoints...
Displacement from PIC
Interference region...
Adjusting the center of
gravity 6cm forward...
And reignite the leg booster
balance at minus 4.
She's not here, either...
Oh?
Kanzashi-san! So is that it?
Thrust compensation isn't working! Why?
Come, Byakushiki!
Onne-chan....
No... No...
I still can't catch up with her...
As expected, I'm still not good enough.
Kanzashi!
O-Orimura-kun.
This hurts a lot...
Umm...
You alright?  Kanzashi-san?
What? Y-yes.
That's good.
I figured this was going
to happen, but now
we've got to submit a report.
Umm, it's my fault.
Don't worry about it.
It was an airframe-related accident.
You couldn't help it.
Umm...
Thank you.
What?
You saved me earlier.
Oh, that? That's expected.
What's wrong,  Kanzashi-san?
Nothing.
More importantly, I bet you're hungry.
Let's go get something to eat.
Thank you for the food.
So you soak your kakiage
in the soup, huh?
Laura likes it crispy, so
if she sees you doing that,
there would be a battle.
No, this is "soaking the entire
body in the bath" style.
That's a new faction.
Excuse me then.
Oh yeah, do you want to
try my chicken nanban?
Huh?
It's fresh and hot. It's the best.
Just give it a try. Say "ah".
It's delicious, isn't it?
Hey, can I have some of your kakiage?
I'm eating it...
Sorry.
I didn't know you liked it that much.
I'm not giving this to you.
Therefore, the most important elements
in combat are weight, speed and flow.
I not only let him feed me,
Those three things are believed
to be the most crucial elements.
but I also kissed him indirectly!
What do I want?
What's going to happen to me?
If you don't know, you
should give it a try.
Team up with me, Kanzashi-san.
No, I mean... I don't
know... I  just don't know.
But if you keep saying that
you'll never find out.
That's true, but...
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Just leave it to me.
Come on. Team up with me, Kanzashi.
Oh?
I did it! I got you to team up with me!
Well...
All right! We'd better
dash to the staff room.
We're going to register our partnership!
How much of your airframe
has been completed so far?
The weaponry isn't done yet.
Besides, operation data
isn't even available yet,
so it still can't be used
in real combat as-is.
I see. What do you mean by "weaponry"?
High-speed guided missiles
controlled by a multi lock system.
Also a charged particle cannon.
But it's not done yet, either.
A charged particle cannon!
We can use Byakushiki's data.
Let's see, this one is
for Yukihira Nigata...
Oh, there it is!
We'll get operation data
later, so for now,
let's start it up with
whatever we can use.
Okay.
Thank you very much!
Don't worry about it.
Let's go take a shower.
What? No!
Come on. Don't be like
that. There, there.
P-Please don't pull me!
I can walk by myself!
Long ago, she used to pull my hands like this..
I hurt that person.
This feels so good,
don't you think, Houki-chan?
What are you thinking about?
What? Oh, I was
just thinking about my sister...
Houki-chan, about your onee-san,
are you keeping your distance from professor Tabane?
I don't hate her.
I also appreciate the fact that she
gave me her personal IS.
I see. That's good to know.
After all, one should try to be good on terms with their family.
Not that I'm in any position
to say that to anyone.
But I still don't know
what she's thinking.
Are you scared because you don't know?
I understand. I feel the same way, too.
What?
It's okay. You shouldn't worry.
I'm sure Onee-san still cherishes you.
Hey, let's ask the Maintenance staff
to help us tomorrow.
We don't have much time
left until the match.
Safety first, right?
Sure. Let's do that.
Shall we go home now, Kanzashi-san?
What's the matter?
Don't use san...
Huh?
Just "Kanzashi" is fine!
What?
I actually said it....
I'm weird!
I might like him...
Hi!
We came to help you!
Thank you for coming today.
Orimura-kun, go out on a date with me!
What?
Kan-chan!
Honne, sorry about
the last minute request.
What are you apologizing for?
I'm going to work really hard
for you today, Kan-chan!
Thank you!
All right. Since we don't
have a lot of time,
why don't we get right to it?
Orimura-kun, bring me the
extra large wrench
and the high-frequency cutter?
Y-yes!
Please give me the data scanner
and the ultrasonic wave tester!
Y-yes!
Orimura! Bring me a juice!
Yes!
Orimu! Bring me some candy!
Okay.
Can you go get me a shampoo
from the school store?
That has nothing to do with this!
I guess this will do.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
I couldn't have done it alone.
Thank you so much!
Don't mention it.
After all, we're fellow students
of the same school, you know.
Well, let us get out of here now.
Orimu, please clean up.
I guess we did it.
Yeah... Thanks to everyone...
Let's do our best at the
tournament, Kanzashi.
Yeah!
Ciao!
You randomly came in again?
Ichika-kun, give me a massage.
What?
Ichika-kun, you and my sister are doing just fine.
Where did that come
from all of a sudden?
I say that because Orimura-sensei is
very strict with you in particular.
Do you call that being close?
Hey, you don't get it, do you?
She's strict to you because
she cares about you
and you're special to her...
And so that you won't die.
You know, if a war or
something broke out.
Now you can rub my butt.
Why did you suggest that?!
I just wanted to see that face.
I wonder Orimura-kun would eat this if I gave it to him...
Jeez, give me a break!
It's alright.
By the way, how'd it go
with Kanzashi's airframe?
What's going on?
Well, it's coming together.
My airframe data came in handy, right?
This is all Nee-san's doing...
No way...
Nohohon here.
Today, I'm going to make
myself a personal IS
by using paper and cardboard boxes.
Why don't I give it a name first?
Nohohon's personal IS will be
called "the Fox's Wedding"!
Hey, that's Miss Orimura! Yahoo!
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
"The Requirements for a Hero"