I'm coming too!
Not yet! Just a bit more!
Ichika!
Fire!
You're not getting away!
Chifu-ne-
I'll kill you...
Orimura Ichika.
kitto aeru yo
I'm certain we'll meet once more
egao to namida wo idaite
As we cherish our smiles and tears
kimi to isshoni
Together with you
asu no sora wa nani iro ni kawaru kana
I wonder what color tomorrow's sky will be
jibun no chikara de kagayakasete yukou
Let's make it shine by ourselves
shiranai koto dakara doki doki suru ne
It's exciting because I don't know what will happen
tameshitai motto
I want to keep trying new things
genkai wa kimenakute ii
But we don't need to limit ourselves
kizuite kaze no koe ga oshieru
Listen to what the voice of the wind is telling us
susumou tsugi no monogatari he to
Let's move onto our next story
habataite makesou demo nigetari shinai
Even if it seems I can't win at all, I'll never run away
kimi to kizamu toki wo shinjite yukou
Let's move on believing in the time we spent together
hikari made egao to namida wo idaite
Hold onto the smiles and tears until we reach the light
taisetsu na hito mamoru tame ni tsuyoku nare
I'll become even stronger to protect the ones close to me
What?!
Morning already?
Laura!? You're doing this again—
Today...
Laura
I'm not naked!
What's with the outfit?
A superior officer gave me some advice.
Seriously, get rid of those clothes!
There's only one reason I was waiting for you to wake up.
Look at this.
What's this? Let's see...
The Date of Your Dreams at the End of Summer
Send summer off at Rainbow Island!
.                Summer special event tickets              .
.               Adults ¥‎6200, children ¥‎4100             .
.                   OPEN 08:00-22:00/Until 9.8               .
.              Yukata Rentals available              .
Let your love
burn all the way
Enjoy in
a Yukata
Stalls
for the
adults
"End of Summer Date and Festival"...
Is this an event at the pool in that
amusement park that opened this year?
New Rainbow Island Pool
Let love slide into the two of you!
I wanted to check this place out.
Really? You want to go?
Huh, it looks like you can rent
a yukata at the festival square.
I want you to see me in a yukata...
Then let's go! Everyone can—
What was that about? What'd she get mad about?
Milady, thanks for doing your duty for Britain this summer vacation.
Of course, I'm a Alcott after all.
More importantly...
I've finally returned!
At the end of the day, I simply want to be together
with my special someone under the same sky...
Hey, Cecilia.
I-Ichika-san!
It's been a week, hasn't it?
Good day to you.
Could it be that he came out to greet me?
I just couldn't sit still,
knowing that you were returning!
Ichika-san!
You can't!
We shouldn't do that in a place like this!
Cecilia? Cecilia?
Huh? I'm alright. I just felt a little dizzy for a second.
Oh? I'm glad to hear.
By the way, would you like to go to this tomorrow?
Oh my! Going out with you, Ichika-san?
I, Cecilia Alcott, will be prepared for anything!
Not this again. They aren't aware enough of their position as a bride.
Something wrong, Laura?
No, it's nothing.
Oh yeah! Laura, if you've got some time today,
would you like to go clothes shopping with me?
What are you talking about?
My clothes are my military uniform—
But those are all uniforms.
You need more than military uniforms.
Come on, summer break's almost over. Let's go!
Well, I guess you have a point.
Then, we'll leave around ten, okay?
S-Sure thing.
What do you think?
These clothes are for going out.
So you're still wearing a uniform, huh?
Hey, hey, ever heard of Seaside Park's Dream Crêpes?
I have, I have!
If you eat a mixed-berry one with the person you like
your love will come true!
Right! But it's always sold out.
Love will come true...Mixed-berry?
Cold!
Aw, summer break is ending tomorrow,
and I still haven't made any memories with Ichika...
I mean, he's why I chose to
stay here instead of going back home.
I stayed here instead of flying home, so I wish he'd initiate at least once.
Hey, Rin!
What? Ichika?!
I'm coming in!
W-w-wait a second!
So which do you want Laura, skirt or pants?
Either i—
Don't say either, okay?
I swear Laura, you're just like Ichika when
it comes to that kind of stuff.
It's a good thing for couples to be similar.
First we'll get something for autumn-
Wait! I don't need autumn clothes just yet.
Why?
It's still summer.
I can buy autumn wear in the autumn.
You know, girls are supposed to
get clothes a season ahead.
Really?
I guess it's too late to get equipment
after a war starts. Is that what you mean?
S-sure...
Okay, let's just look at everything then.
Welcome.
Perfect silver, and blonde too!
I mean...
Could I interest you in the newest clothing line?
Whoa, it's light and slightly transparent.
What do you think, Laura?
White is...
It's not bad, but I'm already wearing white.
Since we're here, why don't you try it on?
No thanks, it'd be a hass—
Not a hassle at all!
I may be wrong, but maybe...
I'm not attractive to boys.
How ridiculous.
If I was going to get one, it might as well have been something cute.
Then Ichika would praise me for it.
Laura, that's a cute outfit.
Just...the clothes?
Of course you're the cutest here.
You idiot...
How's it going Laura? You finished?
You still have your uniform on.
Charlotte...
Um, maybe it didn't quite suit you?
No, not exactly...
But...maybe something cuter would be better.
Okay! You want something cute, right?
So, what do you want?
Well...something that's a little revealing would be nice.
Leave it to me!
Whoa, she's pretty...
She looks like a fairy.
Here, Laura.
Getting the shoes out too huh? I'm surprised.
Might as well.
Are you okay?
S-Sorry.
Should I take a photo of this?
M-Me too!
You're welcome.
NEVER FALTER
I am both aware...
and unaware of the way to win.
I want to protect the one who is close to me.
I think my breasts got bigger again.
Houki? You in there?
Ichika?
What is it?
Houki, I've been looking for you!
Can I talk to you for a bit?
Uh, well...give me a moment!
W-What's up?
My bad. I didn't know you were in the shower.
Y-Yeah. So what is it?
Want to go here with me?
It's kinda last minute,
so you don't have to if you don't want to.
Sounds good to me!
Thank you for waiting.
I'm tired.
You should've kept it on.
Um, well...it's like...
I didn't want to get it dirty.
Or could it be you just wanted Ichika to
be the first person to see it?
That's not true at all!
Manager
You two!
Want to work part-time?
Huh?
Why am I dressed as a butler?
Come on, you're much cooler and handsomer than those guys.
Really?
I would have preferred a maid uniform too.
Maybe I'm just this kind of person after all?
Don't worry. You look really good in it!
Y-you think so?
Welcome to Café @ Cruise!
Thank you for waiting!
Would you like black tea?
Sure.
If you have any requests, please let me know, Miladies.
Don't move your hands!
Keep it down!
You're already surrounded!
Come out quietly!
If you want these hostages out alive, get us a car ready!
Make sure to leave off any tracking devices too!
They're afraid.
Hey!
You there!
I'm thirsty. Bring me the menu.
The hell is this?
Water.
What?
Shut up and drink it...
...if you can!
Don't screw around, you brat!
I'll clean you up!
She's not alone...
unfortunately for you!
Target 2, capture complete.
How about on your end, Laura?
No problem. Target 3, capture complete.
This is bullshit!
You've gotta be kidding me! Being stopped by these brats!
Too slow. Die.
All targets, capture complete!
We're saved!
Thank you, Maid and Butler!
Laura, if find out we're Representative Cadets,
we'll be in trouble, so we should leave.
Yeah. Let's leave it to the police.
I'd rather blow this place sky high and die
than get caught and spend the rest of my life in jail!
Checkmate!
You want more?
Your wrists are next.
Excuse me!
Two crêpes please, mixed-berry flavor.
Oh, I'm so sorry, but we're already sold out today!
I see.
Laura, you got anything in mind?
Sure.
Yeah, strawberry and blueberry please.
Sure. Thank you very much!
Hey, this is good!
Yeah, it is. This is my first time eating a crêpe, but I think it's delicious.
I'll come here with Ichika next time.
Hopefully they'll have mixed-berry in stock!
Charlotte.
Hm? What?
L-Laura...
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wha-
You had some sauce on you.
I-I-I know, but still...
Both of my hands are full.
Don't worry about it.
Here, you can have a bite of my crêpe.
T-Thanks.
Oh, by the way, about the crepe shop...
There's no mixed-berry flavor there.
What?
It wasn't even on the menu.
Not to mention, I didn't see any sauce
in the kitchen that would've been used for it.
I-Is that so? You've got a good eye.
But you still got to have mixed berry, didn't you?
I see! Strawberries and blueberries!
That's right.
I see.
Now I know the secret of the mixed-berry
flavor that's always sold out.
Eating a mixed-berry crêpe with your
boyfriend would be nice, wouldn't it?
What...is this?
Are you sure these are pajamas?
So cute!
Laura, you look so good in it!
Don't hold me like that! It's hard to move!
Nope.
Cats are supposed sit nice and quietly on people's laps.
Note: In Japanese, "nyan" is the sound of a cat's meow.
Why don't you say "nyan" to get into character?
I-I refuse!
Why should I have to do stuff like that?
What? But it'd be cute.
C'mon, c'mon, say it. "Nyan."
Ny-nyan.
Laura, you're too cute!
Yes! Come in.
Hey there!
Those are some unusual outfits.
A black cat and a white cat.
The two of you look, how do I put it, interesting....
and rather cute!
C-Cute?
R-really? So we're cute!
If you say so...then it's not so bad.
I'll wear it every now and then.
Oh, that's right. It's tomorrow but...
Intruder detected in Area 6-D!
Intercept immediately!
Repeat: Intruder detected in Area 6-D!
Can you hear me?
Listen. Your body has been fitted
with supervisory nanomachines.
Carry out your mission as ordered.
There she is!
What a pain.
Can't kill me, can you?!
Good girl, M.
I'm looking forward to seeing more.
What is your objective?
She's taking on an IS suit-less?
I'm here to take the IS
that's been sealed away in this base...
The Infinite Stratos.
W-What?
Deploy!
Silent Zephyrus!
Could it be Phantom Task?!
Ichika was surprisingly aggressive about it.
He's so helpless, getting flustered asking me on a date.
Hey, everyone!
Sorry I'm late!
I asked Dan and the others as well while I was at it, but they said they couldn't make it.
You idiot!
I'm the idiot for expecting anything!
Playing with the hearts of girls, you're the worst!
I thought it would be something like this...
You fail as a bride!
What's going on?
Ichika-san!
You okay?
I'm fine. Now, shall we hurry and head to the pool?
But where's everyone else?
Everyone's there already.
So we should hurry up and go!
O-Okay.
Quickly! Quickly! Quickly! Quickly! Quickly! Quickly!
I see, you're in a hurry to go in the pool.
All done!
Then let's go!
Cecilia's a nice person for buying us these, isn't she?
Indeed.
Huh? Where is she?
Come to think of it, I haven't seen her.
You don't think...
She tricked us!
We need to split into two groups and look for them.
Pools really are the best in the summer.
Hey, I haven't seen anyone up until now. Are you sure they're here?
Gulp.
T-That's odd, isn't it?
Cecilia!
Where did they go?
No good. They're not here either.
Alright, let's look over there.
What's with you all of a sudden?
That really was close!
Oh, it's Orimura.
Hey there!
Nohohon-san! You all came!
Many of the girls from the IS Academy are here.
Ooh, captain, Cecelia's wearing a perverted swimsuit.
She really did!
How bold!
How erotic, Cecilia!
I-I'm not like that!
Orimu, bye-bye!
Cecilia?
Huh?
We finally found you.
Here, this way!
W-Wait!
Oh!
What is it?
This is called the pair-slide course.
Wow, looks fun.
We've got no choice. I guess we can slide together.
That's unfair, Houki!
Let's play Rock-Paper-Scissors for it.
Fine with me.
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Okay, let me explain the pair-slide.
First, the guy sits here.
Huh? Okay.
And then, the girl sits between his legs.
O-Okay!
U-Um...
Um, like this?
And then the guy holds the girl tightly from behind, like this.
Embrace!
Huh?
Huh!?
I see...
Are you ready Charlotte?
S-Sure, anytime!
S-Sorry!
N-No, it's fine...
Come on, it's dangerous so you need to stay close together.
What?!
Well then, enjoy the ride!
I-Ichika!!
It's not on purp-
U-Um...
Sorry.
Ichika, you perv.
It wasn't on purpose!
It was inevitable!
But you still touched them...
You're late, Ichika. What are you doing?
Alright, let me explain the pair-slide.
First, the guy sits down. Then, the girl sits between his legs and the guy grabs her from behind.
Say, Houki?
Would you mind sitting behind me?
Isn't that backwards?
Well the water's pretty strong;
It might be best for you to hide your face behind me.
Alright, I got ya.
The tighter you hold on, the safer you are.
Um, is this okay?
Y-Yeah...
H-Hey...
Well then, enjoy the ride!
Wow, that was really fast, wasn't it?
Y-Yeah...
What's wrong? Did you get hurt?
No...umm...
Your back's...gotten bigger.
What about my back?
Ichika! Hurry and get up here!
How many times do I have to do this?!
Seriously, running into them even here.
Orimura-sensei, is it okay that you aren't with Ichika-kun? He is your little brother.
This is my day off. If I have to deal with them it'll be a waste.
What is it?
Right. I'll head there right now.
What happened? Is it an emergency?
Yeah.
Green Day Market
Ichika!
So pretty! What are these?
I've never seen them before.
It's called goldfish-scooping.
You use this to scoop goldfish.
Looks like fun!
Ichika, teach me.
Yeah, sure.
Me as well.
Okay, okay. Wait your turn.
Like this.
If this happens, it's game over.
R-really now?
I-I get it now.
How beautiful...
Not the devil fish.
You eat the octopus...
This is traditional Japanese food.
Tasty, isn't it? See, Laura?
This is pretty good.
Delicious!
Now it's my turn to say "ahhn" at Houki.
W-What?
Ichika-san, "ahhn".
Hey, you there!
No one can shoot sharper than I!
That's a toy gun, though...
Oh, as expected of you!
I'm also pretty good at this.
I've had some marksmanship training in the military, of course.
Houki.
What?
Have you gotten better at shooting?
What about you?
I'm a close combat fighter.
So am I.
So it's fine to be bad at shooting.
Yeah!
Damnit.
Oh, that one might be too hard.
No, I have to defeat it!
We'll cover you, Laura.
We have no choice.
Well, only this once.
Yeah!
Then I'll join the battle too.
Form up!
All together, aim!
FIRE!
We did it!
The summer is over, huh?
It looks like it's my debut.
I am Sarashiki Tatenashi.
Go higher, gaze up through the beautiful sky,
takaku motto beautiful sky
Our gaze will make it all the way through
suki tooru manazashi e
mamoritai kagayaki ga kyou mo
The light I want to protect
chikara ni naru yo
becomes my power once again today
naranda kaze ni kimi wo kanjiru
I can feel you in the breeze
sonzai ga ureshii
Your very being makes me happy
shinkokyuu shite miageru sora wa
When I take a deep breath and gaze into the sky
mainichi chigau kao nan da
It looks different every time
doko made mo ikeru ne
We can go anywhere
egaiteku koko kara
We just have to pace it out from here
kinou yori tsuyoi jibun de itai
I want to be stronger than I was yesterday
itsu demo
All the time
takaku motto beautiful sky
Let's go higher into the beautiful sky
suki tooru manazashi ni
Our gaze will make it all the way through
kono shunkan wo yakitsukete iku
Let's burn this moment into our hearts
hikaru motto Beautiful Sky
Let's bring more light into this beautiful sky
tsubasa goto dakishimete
I'll embrace you and your wings
mamoritai kagayaki ga kyou mo
Since the light we want to protect
chikara wo kureru
gives us our strength today
kitto otagai sono yokogao wo
We probably both use each other's face
tegakari ni shiteru ne
as a clue to find each other
hitomi no naka no mirai wo misete
Show me the future within your eyes
mae ni dake nobiteyuku michi
As the road only stretches forward
sono yume wo shinjiru
I'll believe in that dream
tamerawanai kimeta no
I decided I won't hesitate
kasanaru omoi
Our feelings eventually add up
kimi no yuuki ni naretara
I wonder if I gave you the courage
dakara kyou ga precious memory
That's why today is a precious memory
Ever since we jumped
owaranai mabushisa e
tobikonda ano toki kara zutto
into that endless light
sasaeatte precious memories
Let's support each other and make more precious memories
nukumori ga koko ni aru
The warmth is right here
sodatteku kankeichi
Our relationship only grows
chanto uketometai yo
I want to be able to take it in properly
atarashii sora
This new sky
nobashita kiseki
Stretches out like a miracle
tooku made
So far away
kimi no senaka wo ushiwanai zettai
I won't ever lose the sight of your back
takaku motto beautiful sky
Let's go even higher into the beautiful sky
suki tooru manazashi ni
Our gaze will make it all the way through
kono shunkan wo yakitsukete iku
Let's burn this moment into our hearts
hikaru motto Beautiful Sky
Let's bring more light into this beautiful sky
I'll embrace you and your wings
tsubasa goto dakishimete
mamoritai kagayaki ga kyou mo
Since the light we want to protect
chikara wo kureru
gives us our strength today
koko ni shikanai kizuna ga aru ne
since these bonds will remain with us here
Next Time
Painkillers for the Heart