Well, I thought I should use this
opportunity to take your Byakushiki.
Huh?
Just hand it over already!
Just who are you?
Me?
I'm the mysterious beauty, disguised
as someone from a corporate business.
Aren't you happy?
Byakushiki!
I've been waiting for you to use that!
The Mysterious Lady
Take that!
You're pretty good!
If I remember correctly,  you're Makigami-san
from "Mitsurugi", right?
I used the name Makigami
because I had no other choice.
I hope you won't be freaked
out by this, you little brat!
What? IS!?
That's right.
It's "Arachne". Her
poison is pretty strong!
Here!
What's the matter with you?
What? Don't you know?
I might be from an evil organization.
This is not a joke!
I'm not joking, you little brat!
I'm Lady Autumn from the secret organization Phantom Task.
Remember me?
Phantom Task?
You still don't know?
Alright, I'll tell
you before I kill you!
I got you!
Why you!
She's got too many arms!
The armor is pretty solid, too...
If that's the case...
What?
Alright. Let's keep it going!
Trying to be cute with me, huh?
I can't let this go on!
This is bad!
Pretty good, you little brat!
Shut up!
That was dangerous! Too close!
An unidentified IS has been
detected in the locker room!
As expected, they came during the school festival.
but who'd have thought
it'd be just one of them?
Yamada-sensei, watch out
for enemy reinforcements.
Tell  the general
student body to evacuate.
Roger that!
Jeez!
Where the heck Ichika go?
He sure ran quickly.
You guys were just hindering my bride and I.
More importantly, this happened because you covered for Ichika
Well, but...
An unknown IS has been
detected in the locker room
and is currently engaged
in battle with Byakushiki.
All students with personal
IS' must deploy and stand by!
Understood!
Alcott and Fang, you two go on patrol!
Yes, ma'am!
Shinonono, Dunois and Bodewig
are to support Orimura.
Head towards to the locker room!
Understood!
All right, let's go.
The enemy's movement is...
Your speed is dropping.
This is...
Shift to a straight-line maneuver from
the circular orbit of your Shooter Flow.
Now I know the timing!
You annoying brat!
Now! Ignition boost!
You're just a kid after all.
You came at me head-on.
Damn it...
This is a piece of cake!
That's what you get for
underestimating the spider's web!
Now it's time for some entertainment.
Well...
Allow me to take your Byakushiki.
I'll tell you something
else while I'm at it.
The people who kidnapped you
during the Second Mondo Grosso
was  Phantom Task!
This is an emotional reunion indeed!
Why you...!
Now that I'm through
with you, I'll kill you!
That would problematic.
because Ichika is my favorite.
Where did YOU enter from?
I thought all the systems were locked.
T-Tatenashi-san..
I'm this school's student council president, so I conduct myself as such.
What the hell are you talking about?
Take this!
Starboard side, clear!
It's all clear over here, too!
Spotted an IS approaching at high speed!
Prepare yourselves, both of you!
Yes, I understand!
Let's stop it!
IS confirmed!
We'll be there right away!
There's no way...!
BT Second, Silent Zephyrus?!
What's the matter, Cecilia? Shoot it!
O-okay!
What's going on with that?
This is also from us!
That was...!
BT weapon, "Flexible"?! Impossible!
Amongst all current pilots, I'm supposed to have the highest BT compatibility rate.
So why...
Cecilia, it's dangerous, run!
Tatenashi-san!
How dare you do that to her!
You... show no reaction?
This is... water?
That's correct.
It's a clone made from water.
Oh I didn't expect that.
That IS has pretty nice mobility.
What's with you!?
I'm Tatenashi Sarashiki...
aka IS "Mysterious Lady". Remember that.
I'll kill you right here right now!
Saying such things already?
Damn it, you little brat!
Don't get carried away!
You'll never beat this water if you use that attack.
It's not just ordinary
water?! What is this?
You're sharp.
This water is being controlled by
nanomachines that transmit IS energy.
Isn't it great?
By the way, do you know something?
In this school, the title of Student council
president is the most powerful you could have!
Who cares!
"The most powerful", you said?
Don't make me laugh!
Tatenashi-san!
Ichika-kun, let me this to me.
Don't be so cocky!
I can't move!
The next blow will end this!
Hey, isn't this room hot?
Huh?
I'm not talking about the temperature,
rather I'm talking about the accumulation of human body heat.
What are you talking about?
How profound it is determined by the level of humidity.
Don't you think it's awfully humid?
Mist can enter the armor
through the cracks.
Yes, that's the face I was looking for.
The face that shows you just
realized that your plan failed.
"Mysterious Lady"...
This machine, which also
means "mist bearing lady",
can control the water freely using
nanomachines that transmit energy.
I'm not done yet!
No, it's already over.
Right, Ichika-kun?
Yukihira Nigata, Maximum output!
Take this!
Ichika-kun, chase them!
Okay!
Damn it!
I came to get you, Autumn!
Where's the respect when you address me?
A new one?
Ichika-kun, don't go!
Who are you?
Orimura-sensei, this machine is...
They're using it already, huh?
I won't let you get away!
You don't know when to quit, do you?
This is it.
It's so strong!
Oh no, the energy is...!
Ichika!
Is this all you've got,
Germany's advanced version?
How do you know about that?
I don't have to tell you.
Is it Squall?
Understood.
Too many of them are ready to attack.
Let's go back, Autumn.
Get out of here, everyone!
Are you okay, Ichika-kun?
Yeah, I think so...
Hey, where did that woman go?
She got away.
It looks like she made only their
equipment and armor shatter.
I see.
Um, by the way,
It'd be great
if you could get off me
Stop it! You're a pervert, Ichika.
I-I-I'm not!
It was just an emergency!
That isn't very manly!
So what do you think of my boobs?
What? Well, umm,
they were really soft...
Ichika-kun.
Y-yes!
Pervert!
The extracted the core, then destroyed the IS Arachne.
The other one appeared to be Silent
Zephyrus, the Blue Tears II,
which was stolen in England.
The people called "Phantom Task", huh?
Yes. Their next target
appeared to be Byakushiki.
There are so many things that
we don't know about Byakushiki.
Right.
I had Sarashiki train and
safeguard Orimura, but...
I bet you were worried the whole time.
Maybe you wished you
could take her place.
Don't be ridiculous.
That's Sarashiki's responsibility anyway.
Sure.
I didn't need your help!
You need to stay out of my way!
Say something, you brat!
YOU!
Stop it, Autumn.
You're too loud.
Squall...!
You need to calm down.
It ruins your beautiful face.
It's stupid.. It's worthless...
M, send Silent Zephyrus to maintenance.
It still needs some modifications.
Okay.
Very, very soon...
I'll begin my revenge.
That's right. I will
finally be able to reunite with her.
That's why I was always around you.
So I could protect you.
I didn't know that.
The Sarashiki Family has always been
well known for working secret
operations like this.
But...
It looks like the immediate danger is
gone for now so I'll get to relax a bit.
I'm sorry for being so clingy.
It's fine.
Would you be lonely if
I stopped being around?
What?
Well...
By the way, guess what this is!
That crown!
Yup, that's right.
A wonderful item!
This crown lets whoever holds it
to live in the same room with you!
What? No one told me
anything about that!
That's true, because I only
told that to the girls.
What are you thinking?!
Either way,
I'm the one who got it.
Oh, no way...
Good night, Ichika-kun.
It's so nice of you to have me here.
Teke-ten-ten-ten-ten!
I'm Lingyin Fang!
There's this boy, a childhood
friend named Ichika Orimura,
and he just never seems to get ahead.
And to make matters worse,
he's totally crazy about me.
Who knows where he's wandering
around again today?
Miss Chifuyu...!
Lovely Style
Next time on Infinite
Stratos 2, "Lovely Style"