Each drive part's response is bad.
But why?
The aptitude level of the
core isn't rising either.
Should we not go towards this type?
I might as well go home and
watch anime or something.
Sisters
Yahoo, Orimura-kun and Shinonono-san.
Mayuzumi-san, what's up?
Well, I've got a favor to ask of the two of you.
A favor to ask Ichika and me?
Yes, that's right.
My older sister works part time
at a publishing company,
and I was wondering if she could
exclusively interview you two
since you have your own IS'.
This is the magazine that she works for.
Um, does this magazine have
anything to do with IS?
What's this?
Is this the first time you have done this type of work?
No.
THOSE GORGEOUS IS PILOTS
You know, some people with personal
IS' actually do talented things.
They're almost like pop idols.
They mainly model though.
Is this true, Houki?
Don't ask me! I don't know!
I can show you guys a photo of me modeling.
Rin!
I'll decline the offer.
What!?
I'm sure you look really
cocky in the photos.
What did you just say?
Fine, look at one and see for yourself!
Look at one now!
Look at them right now!
Hey, that's pretty good.
See? See?
And this one... This one's from
the summer event last year...
I looked a little sexy.
I'll be back after school!
And check this one out.
Owww...
Go back to Class-2 already.
Okay.
Well,
I'd like to begin the
theory lecture regarding
the most effective methods
to keep your
distance in close combat.
Hey, did you hear
about the upcoming event
exclusively for the people
with personal IS?
What? Really?
I've heard that Kanzashi-san
from our class is participating.
What? But I thought her personal
IS hasn't been completed yet.
It'd be good if she got it on time.
Hey, Houki.
What?
What should we do about
Mayuzumi's request?
I'm turning down the offer.
To be part of an exhibition like that would be going against my principles.
As expected.
Yahoo! Sorry to keep you  waiting!
Anyway, about the interview...
About that, Houki is..
Ta-da! As a reward, you'll get a free dinner
invitation to this
three-star restaurant.
And of course it's for two.
Umm, I'm sorry to tell you this, but...
We'll do it!
Huh?
So it's decided!
The interview will happen
on Sunday, thanks!
Umm, well...
See ya!
Houki, what happened to your principles?
Well, I'm just a very flexible
thinker. That's all.
Flexible, huh?
Going to complain about that?
Well, I guess it's fine as
long as you're okay with it.
All right...
By the way, about this dinner...
We're going together, right?
Sure. Why not? Since I'm
being interviewed, too...
Really? Right.
You're absolutely right.
Give me his location!
No, I'll never tell you!
Okay, then...
That's enough!
What?!
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Just leave it to me.
I believe that some day
he'll come for me.
Why you...!
Are you okay?
Y-yes.
Thank goodness.
My own hero who will see me and save me.
Hi there, I'm Nagisako Mayuzumi, the
assistant editor of "Infinite Stripes".
Thank you for coming today.
Oh, hello. I'm Ichika Orimura.
I'm Houki Shinonono.
All right, let's start
with the interview.
Are you ready for the first question?
Orimura-kun, What are your thoughts on going to an all girls highschool?
Well...
I have trouble finding
bathrooms I can use.
I guess what my sister told me was true!
I see.
I'd like to ask you about
your sister, Shinonono-san.
What are you thoughts about receiving
a personal IS from your Onee-san?
Have you considered becoming a
representative candidate for any country?
I am grateful for Akatsubaki.
I'm not interested in becoming a
representative candidate at the moment,
although that opportunity has often been offered to me.
Okay, okay.
Orimura-kun, Shinonono-san, I wonder which one of you is stronger.
I am!
Is that right?
Well, yeah...
Isn't that bad for the hero?
I'm not really a hero.
I'm just another private
first class graduate.
Hey, I like that line.
Okay, Captain Orimura, tell me
your motto on the battlefield.
Well, umm...
I'll... protect my friends!
Yes! That sounds so cool!
Okay, let's move on to the photo shoot.
I'll protect Houki!
I see, I see, I see!
For Shinonono
This is what I'm supposed to wear!?
Me?! Really, me?!
However
This might be a good opportunity.
All right!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Shinonono-san is coming!
I-Ichika, wait long?
S-sure.
That looks good on you.
What I mean is that, it's not bad.
Oh, thank you.
You look cute as well, Houki.
Ichika complimented me!
Okay! Let's get the photo shoot started!
Get closer, you two. Closer.
Um, like this?
No, that's won't do! Even closer! Even Closer!
Okay.
That's it. I want it
to have an adult feel.
Okay, next. Orimura,
hold Shinonono's waist.
What?
Hold her waist! Quickly!
Y-yes, ma'am!
Good, very good.
Okay, next. Shinonono-san, put your
arms around Orimura-kun's neck.
Get to it!
We've took some great photos!
Umm...
Good job, guys. I'm giving you the clothes.
Thank you so much for everything today.
Great job!
Shall we go home?
I guess.
We were staring at each
other, so close together.
If we had actually been
alone at the time...
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Did you sprain it?
It's not that bad.
The heel came off.
Then I'll just take the
other heel off, too.
There. That's better.
Ouch...
Don't force yourself.
It couldn't be helped, you had to
wear shoes you weren't used to.
Here.
What?
Thanks, Ichika.
Don't be modest.
After all, it's my job to protect you.
We did a lot today huh?
She fell asleep.
I like you, Ichika...
Hmm?
I really have no choice.
I'm coming in, M.
Can you explain the
unauthorized contact
from the other day, Madoka Orimura?
Your duty is to seize
other countries IS.
If you choose to act
for any other reason...
You always had good reflexes.
It doesn't matter whether
you're Madoka Orimura or not.
Right now we need you to
be "M" of Phantom Task.
That's my intention until
I settle the score.
Settle the score... with Ichika Orimura?
He's not a threat.
I can kill him anytime I feel like it.
Then I guess it's about settling
the score with Chifuyu Orimura?
Chifuyu Orimura, huh?
Since she no longer has her own IS,
I can't see any situation where you would have a hard time dealing with her.
Don't underestimate her.
You're no match for her.
I guess I'll get some more sleep.
Be quiet until your next task.
Understood.
I like an obedient girl.
Who are you?
My name is Madoka Orimura.
Chifuyu-nee...
How many times do I
have to tell you this?
It's "Orimura sensei"!
Actually, about our family...
Do you think that there's
more to our family than just you and me?
Like, an imouto or something.
You're my only family.
The entire school will be participating
in a tag-team tournament
designed to improve the skills
of each pilot with a personal IS.
Tag-team tournament?
Many IS have been hijacked
around the world.
Even one of ours was
targeted during the cultural
festival the other day.
That is why those of you with
personal IS need to increase
your skill level.
That is all.
I-Ichika, I made too
much food for my lunch,
would you like to have some?
Wow, are you sure, Charl?
Of course!
Here, Ichika.
Thank you.
This is delicious.
Charl, you've gotten good at making Japanese food.
Really? Thank you, Ichika.
Hey, this is delicious, as well.
The batter is so crispy.
There you are, Ichika.
Now, try my Chinese stir-fry with
green peppers and meat, too.
Whoa, it looks delicious!
Doesn't it?
Tasty! It's really tasty, Rin!
You two are great at cooking,
the two of youwill become great housewives.
Hey, Ichika, try my omelet, too.
Have some tea, too.
Why are both of you being
so nice to me today?
Well, that's because...
Aren't we always?
You think so?
Hey, Ichika.
Tell me what kind of partner you
think is easy to fight alongside?
Let's see...
My shooting skills aren't that good yet.
so it'd be nice if my partner could
cover me in that particular area.
But in the end I guess it's all
about compatibility
and working in harmony.
C-compatibility?
What do you guys think?
I think my partner would be
someone who could save me
when I'm being cornered...
Someone who would fight
for me with their life...
I see.
As expected, I'm also the same as Rin.
Oh, and I'd want my partner
to be on the ball!
So, that's your type, huh?
Boy, today's training sure was tough.
Ichika-kun, umm...
Please take care of my sister!
Huh?
Anyway, this is her.
Her name is Kanzashi Sarashiki.
I see.
She's kind of negative.
Okay...
But she has skills.
She's a representative
candidate of Japan, but...
But?
She doesn't have her personal IS.
Because of you, Ichika.
What?
Kanzashi-chan's personal IS was to be
built by the same developer that made Byakushiki.
So all the workers were
sent to work on Byakushiki
and hers got put on the back burner.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
So, I want you to pair up with
Kanzashi in the upcoming
tag-team tournament.
Please!
Hey, Tatenashi-san, please raise your head.
So, it's alright with you?
Um, so you want me to go
ask your sister, Kanzashi,
to be my partner?
Yes, but don't mention my name.
Why not?
Well....
Don't tell me.
You're not on good terms with your imouto?
I understand.
I'll approach her as
naturally as possible.
Great, thanks.
I've been waiting for you, Ichika.
Naturally you'll be pairing up with me
for the tag team tournament right?
Well, actually...
This is the entry form.
Put your signature on it, now.
I'm sorry, Laura, but I've already
decided who I'm pairing up with.
What...
You are my bride, yet you would
pair up with someone else?!
I don't want to smell the scent of
burnt flesh anywhere outside
of a BBQ restaurant!
Instructor, this is a problem
for a married couple!
Don't give me that married couple crap, you idiot!
I don't want a sister-in-law
with no manners like yourself.
The instructor doesn't like me anymore.
Hey, Orimura, carry
Bodewig back to her desk.
I'm going to start the class now.
You're too slow, Ichika! I'm over here!
It's over, Ichika!
Not yet! Not Yet!
I beat Ichika.
He said something about already
having chosen me to be
his tag-team partner.
If he insists, I would consider it...
Ichika said he'd already decided
who he was going to pair up with.
so his partner must be me!
Finally, Finally I get
to do something with Ichika...
You must be in a really
good mood, Cecilia.
Hi, Houki-san.
How's life?
Not bad.
How about you, Houki-san?
It's been alright.
When she hears that Ichika's
teaming up with me.
Good for you.
Poor Houki...
She has no idea that
Ichika is going to pick me
Later, Cecilia.
Good day to you.
I win!
Hey, that's Orimura from Class-1.
Do you need someone in Class-4?
Is Sarashiki-san here?
Umm...
Nice to meet you. I'm Ichika Orimura.
I know.
What?
State your business.
Oh, yeah.
For the upcoming tag team tournament,
do you want to partner up with me?
No.
Don't say that. Please.
I have the right to punch you,
but I won't because it's too tiresome.
Hi! Good morning, Sleepyheads!
Today it will be sunny then
cloudy, with periods of rain.
Don't forget your umbrella!
All right, everyone! Have a nice day!
Smooch!
Oh, my, if it isn't Miss
Orimura. Is something wrong?
Next time on Infinite Stratos
2, "Open Your Heart"
Open Your Heart