And...?
There, there, Rin, calm down.
Come on. You're scaring Kanzashi.
Stop it, Charlotte.
Normally I'd torture her
or administer a truth serum,
but I'm just barely resisting.
Don't say stuff like that!
Here you go, Kanzashi-san.
I bet you're thirsty.
Oh, thanks.
So, what is the truth?
What?
S-s-so basically, are y-y-you
and Ichika actually...
...d-d-d-dating?!
Ichika and I aren't like that...
"I-I-Ichika"?!
She addressed him so casually!
Well that's not what I'm hoping happens, but anyways
It looks like we read too
much into it, didn't it?
I must apologize, Sarashiki-san.
Y-you can call me Kanzashi.
Then you can call us by
our first names, too.
O-okay.
Since we're in all in the same grade,
why don't we get together for
the practical training after school?
Sure... Thank you.
Cooking My Way
I apologize for being late Orimura-kun.
Everyone should be here soon.
Here's the tape measure.
Yamada-sensei what is this all about?
"What is this all about"?
Well, that's for taking
body measurements.
In the wake of the sudden attack
by the unmanned airframes,
we realized that we must
improve the IS suits
and meticulous measurements
are necessary for that.
I understand that!
That's not the issue I'm having here.
Why am I being measured?
Well, I was skeptical about it, but the
student council had already decided it, so...
What?
INVINCIBLE
What are they thinking? This school...
Why are you being so loud?
Chifuyu-nee!
It's " Orimura Sensei".
Can you even fulfill a
work given to you to
a satisfactory extent?
Health Newsletter Vol. 58
The Usage of School Nurse Office
No, this is clearly not a duty!
I was tricked into this!
Don't give me that hopeless look.
Oh yeah. Let me give you something good.
Wow, a blindfold!
See ya later.
Thank you,  Chifuyu-nee!
Thank you,  Orimura-sensei!
Hey, it's see-through!
Chifuyu-nee!
Hey, that's Orimura-kun.
What? Is he really going to
take our measurements?
Yahoo, Orimu!
Everyone, please quiet down.
I want each of you to strip down to your
underwear to get your measurements taken.
What?!
I'll be in the back taking records,
so you just tell me the numbers.
What?
Wait,  Yamada-sensei...
No. 1, Kiyoka Aikawa, here I come!
Whoa, wait! Wait a minute!
It's too late!
Oh yeah, I shouldn't look while doing this.
It's the mind's eye. My third eye!
Orimura-kun!
All right!
I-I'm going to put the tape
measure around your body,
so spread your arms out a little.
Okay.
Let's see...
Is it around here?
What?
Oh? What is this buzzing?
Orimura-kun, where do you
think you're touching?!
You tell me!
I-I just want to put the tape measure
around your back.
That's not it!
Then where is it?
It's kind of soft.
Hey, stop it, Orimura-kun!
Ichika! How dare you...!
What are you doing?!
I can't believe you.
Ichika, do you have any last words?
What? Oh?
I'm so shocked.
My waist has grown 5 millimeters.
I've gained some weight, too.
Although my bust size remains the same...
If the body slacks, the heart also slacks.
I must increase my training time!
Girls sure worry about strange things.
I can't tell any of those things
by looking at you anyway.
How could you be so insensitive, Ichika?
Oh?
What are you eating today?
The bento box Houki
gave me this morning.
When did Houki do it?
She can't be underestimated.
I-I just happened to
cook too much, so...
I really appreciate it.
Houki's fried chicken
is especially good.
Hmm? Really now?
And Rin's sweet & sour
pork is awesome, too.
Charl's Pot-au-feu was also tasty.
Everyone is so skilled at cooking.
Umm, what about me?
Cecilia, you're...
Hey, it might be best for you to say
that her cooking is murderous!
There's no way I could tell her that!
But that's for  peace! for all of mankind!
What are you whispering, you two?
Ichika-san, tell me what you
think about my cooking!
Everyone, I'm sorry I'm late!
I've brought Kanzashi, too.
H-hello.
Hey, Kanzashi!
Sit next to me.
So, I thank you in advance!
Cecilia?!
I want to learn everyone's home cuisine
in order to further improve my cooking skills!
Your bento boxes, in particular,
always look and taste so great.
I'd love for you to
teach me how to cook.
I see. It certainly makes me
feel good to hear that.
I'd be glad to help, since you insist.
Thank you so much!
First things first, I'd like to know
how to make fried chicken!
What's that thing?
Premier grade chapon
chicken from Bresse.
I got sent the best chicken.
Actually I already have
some chicken in stock,
so take that home with you for today.
Is that so? That's too bad.
I'll use it during the Christmas season.
Okay, let's get this started.
First, cut the chicken thigh
into bite-size pieces.
Salt it and let it sit for a while.
Meanwhile, I want you to chop
the garlic and ginger.
Note: Word play - the same reading for "Orosu"
means both "grate" and "drop" in Japanese.
Okay!
No.
CANOLA OIL
Heat up the oil.
Okay!
Wrong!
Here is when you take them out of the oil
and let them rest for about three minutes.
I'm sorry, but take care of the rest.
What?
Oh, I see, but I'm too busy right now...
The surface should look
a little more colorful.
Some perfume for aroma.
And this and that for glaze...
MUSTARD
Is it done?
Yes, I just finished.
Wow, it came out looking good.
Go ahead and taste one please.
Shinonono is sick today,
so she's absent.
Houki is absent? That's unusual.
I wonder what's wrong with her.
She sounded fine when I talked to her
on the phone last night.
So, I thank you in advance!
No problem at all.
I just got some ingredients
for pot-au-feu earlier.
I was going to take it to Houki.
Do you want to make it together?
Oh? What happened to Laura-san today?
Shhhh!
She looked exhausted today.
She went to sleep as soon as she came home.
So we're going to do this
while trying not to wake her up.
Cecilia, will you cut diagonal slits
in the sausages?
Like this?
Yes, that's good.
You know what you're doing, Cecilia!
Houki-chan taught me how to do it yesterday.
You learned how to from Houki as well?
Yes, but for some reason she took ill
during the cooking.
I-I see.
I wonder why...
I don't have the slightest clue,
but I'm sure  eating this pot-au-feu
will make her feel better.
Definitely!
I think so, too.
Don't tell me Houki got sick because
she ate Cecilia's cooking...
No, I'm overthinking it!
There's been no problem so far anyway.
Besides, we're cooking together...
You just have to let it
cook like this for a while.
It looks delicious.
Hey, Cecilia, will you keep an eye
on the pot for me?
What's going on?
When Laura has a bad dream,
she moves around a lot.
It needs more color...
Sorry about that, Cecilia.
Laura went straight back to sleep.
It's okay. More importantly,
it just finished.
Whoa, it looks great. Let's try it.
You go ahead.
I must've taken a nap during odd hours.
Charlotte has already gone to sleep.
She must've made it for me.
How nice.
Charl and Laura are both absent?
What's going on with everyone?
Laura-san went to bed really
early last night though.
Now that I think about it,
Houki only told me she
was okay from behind
the door when I went to
check on her yesterday.
I wonder if she ate something bad.
Cecilia, did you hurt you fingers?
What? Oh, this? It's nothing.
B-by the way, Ichika...
Would you like to eat
lunch with me tomorrow?
I'll make a bento and bring it.
What? Well, umm...
Sure I'll eat lunch with you....
Then I'll see you at lunch tomorrow
on the rooftop!
O-okay...
I-Ichika!
Hey, Kanzashi. What's wrong?
Umm, I made you a bento.
It'd be great if you would eat it.
Awesome!
This is magnificent art...!
I can't replicate that.
So, you want me to teach you how to
make sweet & sour pork?
Please, Rin-san!
You're joking right?
Cooking WITH Cecilia?!
That has to be the most deadly
combination in the world!
We don't have time after today.
I want to live though!
D-don't say that.
You're the only one
I can count on, Rin-san!
I'd like to help her since I used to be
a bad cook myself, but...
No way! She's a deadly weapon!
One careless slip means
an invitation to death!
Hey, your fingers...
Oh, this happened while I was
practicing cutting with the knife.
It's no big deal.
Fine, I'll do it! I'll
teach you how to make it!
But remember you need
to taste your own food!
Then you sauté the vegetables
after frying the pork.
Okay!
It's looking good.
Normally I'd increase the heat
until flames come out, but...
Until flames come out?
Yes. Chinese food is
all about firepower!
Although we don't get to do that
with this equipment...
Please leave it to me!
What?
I'm sorry, Ichika-san!
For some reason the food
exploded last night,
so I couldn't make a bento...
Hmm? Explosion?
I really wanted to see you
enjoy my cooking, too...
Then let's make it together now!
We don't have to go buy lunch.
I'll teach you how to
make my favorite dish!
What?
Cecilia, are you ready?
Y-yes! I'm sort of nervous.
Still, we can stop if you don't want to do this.
No, we're already here.
I'll be fine.
Okay. Then take it
gently in both hands...
It's hot.
Wet it thoroughly like this...
L-like this?
Yeah, it looks good.
All right, let's get started.
Okay.
Like this?
Yeah. Now you can pick the topping.
What is this red thing?
A sour plum.
You've never eaten one before?
Huh?
Make it into a triangle
shape, like this.
Let's see... Like this?
You need to be a lighter on it.
Hey, you just laughed, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
You were just so cute.
C-c-cute?!
Stop it, Ichika-san.
Can I see it for a sec?
The key is to squeeze it nice and tight.
That's good enough.
Could please teach it to me again?
It's warm...
Yeah, it's fresh and steamy.
That's not what I meant...
The meat tastes good.
Hey, wine!
So you like it, Dr. Tabane?
Yeah, I guess, except that soup
with the sleeping drug.
Teh heh.
So, have you thought about
supplying  IS' for Phantom Task since I spoke about it?
No way! That would be cumbersome!
Hey, give me some cake.
Then how about this?
You see, I'm mentally and physically
over-engineered.
Chi-chan is about the only person
who's good enough to
physically challenge me.
Don't move!
I see you've got an
interesting-looking one.
What's your name?
Let me guess!
Madoka Orimura, isn't it?
Yeah...
Bingo!
Alright then! I'll make a personal IS for her.
What?
Come back to my place with me.
I can have her, right?
That would be a problem...
Bummer! You're so stingy. Oh well...
Hey, Madocchi, what kind of
personal IS do you want?
A long-distance type?
A close-combat type?
How about a special-armored type?
I guess we can talk about that later.
I'll introduce you to Ku-chan.
Let's eat something together!
Yeah!
Now I'd like to begin the
special after-school class.
What's the matter? Are you nervous?
You know you really have to focus!
You-need-to-try-to-focus!
M-Miss Orimura?
Looking For Memories
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
"Looking For Memories"