I might like him...
Team up with me, Kanzashi.
My airframe data came in handy, right?
This is all Nee-san's doing?
The Requirements for a Hero
Hmm? She's not here.
Tag Match Tournament
Opening Ceremony
Hello, everyone!
Today is the IS tag team tournament!
I want to see all of you participants
She's not here, either...
do what you've been training for!
Kanzashi, where did you go?
Give it everything you've got!
This tournament is going to
be a learning experience for
those of you who still don't
have your own personal IS.
So please pay close attention!
My airframe data came in handy, right?
You don't have to do anything...
...because I'll do it all.
But I... I, also...
Just stay ignorant.
No!
I can't beat her.
There's no way I can beat her.
But I still have to
go... just for today...
Tag Match Tournament
Opening Ceremony
I hope this will be a meaningful
experience for all of you,
and that concludes the
announcement of the tournament.
Now enough with the formalities...
It's time to announce the
tournament match-ups!
Daryl Casey & Forte Sapphire
Ichika Orimura & Kanzashi Sarashiki
Houki Shinonono & Tatenashi Sarashiki
Charlotte Dunois & Laura Bodewig
Cecilia Alcott & Lingyin Huang
Ichika Orimura & Kanzashi Sarashiki
vs
Houki Shinonono & Tatenashi Sarashiki
Kanzashi!
Maybe she went to the pit..
EMERGENCY WARNING
What's that?
Orimura-sensei! We're under attack!
What are those?
It looks like the same unmanned type
that showed up before.
No, they're actually upgraded versions.
How many?
Five! They emerged at
each arena's pit.
The students with personal IS,
who were standing by, are being attacked!
Damn! They were too quick!
What?
All teachers are to prioritize
the students evacuation.
All the combat-capable instructors
must prepare for deployment!
Understood!
You're pretty bold,
but don't underestimate us!
What's up with her?
Rin-san, fall back!
Get behind me, Laura!
Ch-Charlotte!
What...? Wh-what's going on?
No...
Save me!
Anyone!
Orimura-kun!
Kanzashi! You alright?
You should deploy your IS or you're going
to get caught in the crossfire!
O-okay!
Orimura-kun!
There are so many of these shots!
I...
Together....
I want to fight alongside with you!
Let's push it out and get some distance!
I got it!
This is tough!
Houki-chan, deploy your
fold-out back armor. Push me!
Okay!
Tatenashi-san!
Now!
Tatenashi!
There's a gap in the unmanned unit's armor.
But...
It's alright, Just do it!
Take this!
You haven't seen anything yet!
I still have my trump card!
The armor...!
Houki-chan..
Use everything you've got
to protect yourself!
you're going to get hurt.
B-but...
I'm immortal, you know.
Take the maximum firepower
of my Mysterious Lady!
Don't...!
Mistilteinn Spear, activate!
What's that?
Don't tell me Houki
and the others are...
Watch out!
I'll handle this area.
Kanzashi?!
Orimura-kun, check the condition
of the gate over there.
Understood!
I won't let you pass through here.
Detecting some kind of unknown energy
coming from the arm of the enemy IS!
Problems detected in
shield barrier deployment!
Absolute defense has been nullified!
I guess that's an anti-IS IS, huh?
Orimura-kun!
No way!
No!
How dare you...
How dare you... How dare you...
How dare you!
I won't forgive you!
The core! If I blow that thing away...
I-Ichika?
Ichika!
No... Stop...
This isn't good...
I couldn't do it....
I'm just not good enough...
Ichika, I'm sorry...
I couldn't save you...
I'm so useless.
I'm sorry that I was ever born...
There's no hero in this world.
Onne-chan?
Onne-chan!
I wonder how many years it's been since you
talked to me that way.
Why? It's just...
It's just impossible!
No, it isn't.
It is! There's no hero in this world!
There isn't.
What?
There's no perfect or flawless hero.
Ichika...
The so-called heroes
don't even cry or laugh.
But I'm human, so I cry and laugh.
I lose sometimes, too.
But I refuse to give up!
I'm a human who can fight
without running away.
That's impossible. Aren't
you afraid of dying?
That is pretty scary.
But if I run away, I feel like
I can never be myself.
I'm...
I'm a...
coward!
It's okay.
You may be weak or dirty
or cowardly or disgraceful...
But you're human.
Onne-chan...
Therefore, Kanzashi-chan,
you need
to accept your weaknesses.
If you accept them, you can stand.
Because...
...I'm human?
That's right.
Besides, you're the little sister
that I'm so proud of.
Yeah!
I'll go and do this, Onne-chan!
This is an amulet.
Use it when you really need it.
An Aqua Crystal?
Good luck, Freshman.
Ichika, are you safe?
Ichika!
H-Houki.
Ichika, How is Reiraku Byakuya?
It's no good, no energy left.
Then let's go with Kenran Buto!
If only I could give you some time,
I'll give him time!
Kanzashi!
There's no time for hesistation!
Ichika, give me your hand!
Uchigane Nishiki,
manual guidance system, activate!
Ready Wama Arashi warheads: 1-48!
Initiating manual control!
Lend me your power, Uchigane Nishiki!
It's still coming?!
Akatsubaki, show me your power!
New Equipment Ready to Use:
Variable Output Blaster Rifle
It'd be great if if I didn't get explnations I don't even understand.
That left arm is mine!
I'm leaving the rest to you!
Kanzashi!
It didn't work?
It's the amulet's turn!
Yay!
Cecilia!
Onee-chan!
Kanzashi-chan! Oww...
You shouldn't move. It's not good for you.
That's not a small wound.
Yeah.
I wonder how many years it's been
since we last talked like this.
I guess I'll have to thank Ichika-kun for this.
Why did I ask him to do this?
Did I want to be clingy?
Onee-chan?
What is it?
What's wrong? Your face is turning red.
What?
It must be the sunset.
You think so?
Hey, Onee-chan...
I'm sorry about everything...
I'm such a horrible imouto.
That's not true
You're my precious imouto.
My very strong imouto.
Onee-chan..
Onee-chan....
As expected, they turned out to be upgraded
unmanned airframes.
The cores are unregistered.
We managed to capture two of them.
Tell the government that we
destroyed all of them.
But that might end up
jeopardizing our school.
Hey, now, who do you think I am?
I can protect a school or two...
I bet my life on it.
It's okay... I have to tell him my feelings.
Hey, Kanzashi.
What's up?
Umm...
Ichika, this is for you...
What's this?
Anime?
Well, if you like...
This is nostaglic.
I watched this long ago.
Do you like it?
Yes, I like it...
I see.
...very much!
I said it! I said I like Ichika!
It was okay, right?
I didn't say anything weird, did I?
Anime?
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
There's no way...
I only told him that I liked anime?!
It's tasty, scrumptious and healthy!
Kanzashi's night snack ramen!
Salt flavor, miso paste flavor
and soy sauce flavor!
Miss Orimura, you saw it, didn't you?
Cooking My Way
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
"Cooking My Way"