He comes right back no matter
how many times I push him away!
Her barrage is thin? Good!
Not yet!
I got this!
Good. I'll lay down the pressure
The first practical training
of the second semester...
These two are energetic.
Yeah.
During this match, Orimura-kun is the superior one
No, that idiot isn't even thinking and just throwing out attacks.
Rin!
The next move will finish this.
Got ya!
You're using your shield too much!
Heart Pain Killer
I could have won that!
I guess I need to do something
about the fuel consumption...
Guess who!
What? Who are you?
Alright! Time's up!
You fell for it!
Um, who are you?
See ya!
You'll need to hurry up
otherwise if you'll piss off Orimura-sensei!
So...
this is why you were late?
Well, so basically, this
unknown female student...
I see.
You were late because you
invited a girl you've never met to a conversation
rather than come to class?
No, that's not it!
Dunois! Demonstrate the
Rapid Switch for me now!
What?
I'll begin the demonstration now.
Umm, Charlotte?
What is it, Orimura-kun?
Let's get this started! Revive!
SCHOOL ASSEMBLY
Now, the student council president
will explain the details.
Well, well, things have
been hectic this year,
so I haven't been able to
properly introduce myself yet.
My name is Tatenashi Sarashiki.
I'm your student council president.
Nice to meet you.
SCHOOL ASSEMBLY
AGENDA: SCHOOL FESTIVAL
So, as for this month's cultural festival
Each class will have their own program. Good luck everyone!
DEADLINE COMING SOON!
Well, all the suggestions for
our class program are...
Ichika Orimura's Host Club
Twister with Ichika Orimura
Pocky Play with Ichika Orimura
The King Game with Ichika Orimura
...all declined!
What?
You idiots!
Who came up with these ideas??
I'm excited for them.
What?
She's right!
You should follow through with
your duty to please girls!
What?
Orimura Ichika is our property.
That's right!
Yamada-sensei, these hilariously bad plans won't do huh?
What? Well, I guess...
I'd like the one with the Pocky.
Can I not entrust anyone with anything mundane?
How about the maid café?
L-Laura?
The customers would like it.
Besides, an eatery will let
you earn back the money you spend on it.
I think it's a good idea.
Making Ichika a butler or in charge of the kitchen would be OK.
Huh?
Orimura? As a butler? That sounds great!
What do we about the maid uniforms?
I can sew them together.
Well, it's decided on the servant café!
I agree!
If I just act like it's a maid cafe with unique uniforms, it'll be ok.
Oh, no! It's already time
for the special training!
Hi!
Student Council President?
Don't be so formal.
You can call me Tatenashi.
Wh-what do you want?
I'm going to be your
IS coach for a while.
What?
What's with this all of a sudden?
There are already so many coaches...
I don't need another one.
So do you think you're weak?
I don't think I'm all that weak.
No, you are weak. Very weak.
Therefore to ensure you won't remain weak, I'll train you.
Is that all?
Fine we'll have a match.
If I lose I'll do whatever
you tell me to do.
Sure, no problem.
SIMPLICITY & FORTITUDE RIVAL UNYIELDING
Alright then, all you have to do to  is get me  once on this mat and you win.
What?
On the other hand, if I win if you are unable to continue.
Are you okay with that?
You sure underestimate me, don't you?
I'll win for sure.
Well, then...
I won't hold back.
Whenever you're ready.
At IS Academy, the title of
school council president...
...means one certain thing.
The school council
president, in other words,
the head of all students...
...is the most powerful!
Get it?
This is the third time.
Do you want to continue?
I'm not done yet!
Boys who try hard are cool!
That's nice to know.
Ichika-kun! you pervert!
Ichika-kun, a girl's underwear  is expensive
SIMPLICITY & FORTITUDE RIVAL UNYIELDING
Jeez, where did he go?
He's only my bride.
No way he could be avoiding me  Just no way.
Hey, Riko, you have some
major bedhead back there.
What? Where is it?
I overslept this morning and didn't style my hair.
That's not cool.
If you don't keep up
with your base grooming
Orimura-kun will think badly of you
Personal grooming?
Good.
Oh?
Ooh, so you've become a woman too huh?
I guess you're at that age.
You got it all wrong.  Instructor.
You may think I'm being
frivolous, but I'm not!
Call me Orimura-sensei.
Okay.
By the way, I saw Ichika in the nurse's office in the club building.
"Nurse's office"?
Are you awake?
What are you doing?!
Letting you rest on my lap.
That's not what I'm asking!
Don't worry about it.
Hey!
Target acquired
BRAVO
I like how straightforward you are.
Alright Ichika-kun, let's begin.
O-okay.
Oh? Ichika?
I heard that he was going to
have a special training session
with Laura in Arena 4 today.
Today I'll be Ichika's specialty coach.
Nice to meet you.
Student council president being a coach?
Ichika-san, what's up with that?
This is uh...  I lost in a match.
hmm hmm, I think it was for Ichika-kun.
Oh yeah, there's something that
I need your cooperation with.
"Our"?
"Cooperation"?
Time is running out,
so let's get started.
Charlotte-chan and Cecelia-chan
show me the shooter circle float.
Could a shooting-style battle
stance be helpful to Ichika?
Here we go!
Ichika, please pay close attention.
Here I come, Cecilia!
I'm all ready!
This is...
They're shooting and
manually controlling their
high-level altitude at the same time.
Not only that, they're doing this
while paying attention to both
evading and targeting, so...
Do you get it?
When'd you get there?!
Ichika!
What are they doing?!
Really!?
you guys alright?
Now it's your turn, Ichika.
Good grief!
Here I come!
O-okay.
This is so different...
Alright begin firing.
Ichika!
Ichika, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Cecilia, let's continue, please.
I don't feel like it,
but if you insist...
All right, let's do it again!
Are you doing this because the Byakushiki has long range assault now?
Yeah, that's correct.
But actually that's not the only thing.
An important factor in determining
shooting skills is the
ability to breach armor, correct?
But the maximum output of
his charged-particle gun,
which isn't capable of rapid fire,
is more like a sniper rifle.
In other words, he focuses all of his power into shot.
But it's clear that Ichika does not have good shooting skills.
...you're purposely making him
fight in a close range battle.
That's right. You're pretty sharp.
Man I'm exhausted,.
Welcome home!
Shall I prepare dinner?
Or  a bath?
Or would you like... ME?
Welcome home!
Would you like me?
Or would...
Or would you...
Or would you like...
Or would you like... ME?
What are you planning?
What?
Since I'm your special coach,
I wanna synchronize with
you by sleeping and
eating together with you.
W-well...
Ta-da!
It's just a swimsuit!
Ichika-kun your reaction was so cute.
Yes! Who is it?
It's me!
I've brought some food for you.
Can I come in?
Houki! No! Sorry.
What are you doing, Ichika?
Oh, I get it!
You don't want her knowing you're messing around.
Ichika, you bastard.
you take this random girl back to your room.
Does your perversion reach no bounds?
You should be ashamed of yourself!
Wait, wait! It's a misunderstanding!
I'm sorry, but I'd be pretty mad if you did.
kill Ichika-kun right now.
Wha-!
It's over!
Your center of gravity is off!
Correct that now!
Y-yes, Ma'am!
Ichika you were very yielding with the senior.
Damn it...
Drop your speed.
Concentrate.
All right!
Okay. I see you picked up speed.
Now try to use Ignition Boost.
What?
Ignition Boost!
Shift to a straight-line maneuver
from the circular orbit
of your Shooter Flow.
Break through the opponent's
barrage all at once
and use the charged-particle
gun at point-blank range!
Just wait a second! I can't
do that all of a sudden...
Now!
O-okay!
Owww...
Remember not to suspend the
Shooter Flow while charging.
Difficult isn't it?
No good. You need to learn how.
Get up and try it again.
Okay.
Ichika, you alright?
Oh what is it?
Do you want some tea?
If you can't eat anything, you
should at least drink some tea.
Thanks, Charl...
Anyways, what is that woman up to?
She's got student council work.
Well it's your fault that you provoked her in the first place.
But she didn't have to beat
you up this badly though.
I guess I got what I deserved.
I guess I really am weak.
I need to master it as soon as possible.
I think boys who don't give up are cool..
Yeah, I'm often jealous of you.
Ichika-san you can stop by my room if you're feeling bitter.
I'll help with your troubles, not a problem.
Hey, wait a second, Cecilia!
Ichika, you should come to my room!
I have playing cards!
Wait! I have playing
cards in my room, too.
How about hanafuda cards, Ichika?
I even have tarot cards in my room!
N-no one is around, right? Good.
Ichika, I like you.
I-I like you, Ichika!
Ichika, will you make miso soup for me?
Ichika nyaa I like you a lot nyaa.
Chi-Chifuyu-san?!
Translucent Chord of Cinderella's Heel
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
Translucent Chord of Cinderella's Heel.