He comes right back no matter
how many times I push him away!
Her barrage is thin? Good!
Not yet!
I got this!
Good. I'll lay down the pressure
The first practical training
of the second semester...
These two are energetic.
Yeah.
In this match, Orimura-kun has the advantage.
No, that idiot isn't even thinking.
He's just throwing out attacks.
Rin!
The next move will finish this.
Got ya!
You're using your shield too much!
kitto aeru yo
I'm certain we'll meet once more
egao to namida wo idaite
As we cherish our smiles and tears
kimi to isshoni
Together with you
asu no sora wa nani iro ni kawaru kana
I wonder what color tomorrow's sky will be
jibun no chikara de kagayakasete yukou
Let's make it shine by ourselves
shiranai koto dakara doki doki suru ne
It's exciting because I don't know what will happen
tameshitai motto
I want to keep trying new things
genkai wa kimenakute ii
But we don't need to limit ourselves
kizuite kaze no koe ga oshieru
Listen to what the voice of the wind is telling us
susumou tsugi no monogatari he to
Let's move onto our next story
habataite makesou demo nigetari shinai
Even if it seems I can't win at all, I'll never run away
kimi to kizamu toki wo shinjite yukou
Let's move on believing in the time we spent together
hikari made egao to namida wo idaite
Hold onto the smiles and tears until we reach the light
taisetsu na hito mamoru tame ni tsuyoku nare
I'll become even stronger to protect the ones close to me
Heart Pain Killer
I could have won that!
I need to work on conserving my fuel..
Guess who!
Huh? Who are you?
Alright! Time's up!
You fell for it!
Um, who are you?
See ya!
You need to hurry up
otherwise you'll piss off Orimura-sensei!
So...
why were you this late?
Well, so basically, this
student I have never met before.....
I see.
You were late because you
talked to a girl you've never met
instead of coming to class?
No, that's not it!
Dunois! Demonstrate the
Rapid Switch for me now!
What?
I'll begin the demonstration now.
Umm, Charlotte-san?
What is it, Orimura-kun?
Let's get this started! Revive!
SCHOOL ASSEMBLY
Now, the student council president
will give you an explanation.
Well, well, things have
been hectic this year,
so I haven't been able to
properly introduce myself yet.
My name is Tatenashi Sarashiki.
I'm your student council president.
Nice to meet you.
SCHOOL ASSEMBLY
AGENDA: SCHOOL FESTIVAL
So, for this month's cultural festival
Each class will have their own program. Good luck everyone!
DEADLINE COMING SOON!
Well, the suggestions for
our class program are...
Ichika Orimura's Host Club
Twister with Ichika Orimura
Pocky Play with Ichika Orimura
The King Game with Ichika Orimura
...all rejected!
Huh?
You idiots!
Who came up with these ideas??
I'm excited for them.
What?
She's right!
You should follow through with
your duty to please girls!
What?
Orimura Ichika is our property.
That's right!
Yamada-sensei, these absurd plans won't do right?
What? Well, I guess...
I like the one with the Pocky.
Why can't anyone come up with something normal?
How about a maid café?
L-Laura?
The customers would like it.
Besides, an eatery will
earn back the money you spend on it.
I think it's a good idea.
Making Ichika a butler or in charge the kitchen would be OK.
Huh?
Orimura-kun? As a butler? That sounds great!
What do we do about the maid uniforms?
I can sew them.
Well, it's decided on the servant café!
I agree!
If I just act like it's a maid café with unique uniforms, it'll be okay.
Oh, no! It's already time
for the special training!
Hi!
Student Council President?
Don't be so formal.
You can call me Tatenashi.
Wh-what do you want?
I'm going to be your
IS coach for a while.
What?
What's with this all of a sudden?
There are already so many coaches...
I don't need another one.
So do you think you're weak?
I don't think I'm that weak.
No, you are weak. Very weak.
Therefore to ensure you don't remain weak, I'll train you.
Is that all?
Fine, we'll have a match.
If I lose, I'll do whatever
you tell me to do.
Sure, sounds good.
SIMPLICITY & FORTITUDE RIVAL UNYIELDING
Alright then, all you have to do to is get me on this mat once and you win.
What?
On the contrary if you are unable to continue, I win.
Are you okay with that?
You sure do underestimate me, don't you?
I'll win for sure.
Well, then...
I won't hold back.
Whenever you're ready.
At IS Academy, the title of
school council president...
...means one thing for certain.
The school council
president, in other words,
the head of all students...
...is the most powerful!
Get it?
This is the third time.
Do you want to continue?
I'm not done yet!
Boys who try hard are cool!
That's nice to know.
Ichika-kun! You pervert!
Ichika-kun,
seeing a girl in her underwear will cost you, you know?
SIMPLICITY & FORTITUDE RIVAL UNYIELDING
Jeez, where did he go?
He's my bride.
No way he could be avoiding me.
Just no way.
Hey, Riko, you have some
major bedhead back there.
What? Where is it?
I overslept this morning and didn't fix my hair.
That's not good.
If you don't keep up
with your personal grooming,
Orimura-kun will think badly of you.
Personal grooming?
Good.
Oh?
Ooh, so you've become a proper woman too huh?
I guess you're at that age.
You got it all wrong, Instructor.
You may think I'm being
frivolous, but I'm not!
Call me Orimura-sensei.
Okay.
By the way, I saw Ichika in the nurse's office in the club building.
"Nurse's office"?
Are you awake?
What are you doing?!
Letting you rest on my lap.
That's not what I'm asking!
Don't worry about it.
Hey!
Target acquired.
BRAVO
I like how straightforward you are.
Alright Ichika-kun, let's begin.
O-okay.
Oh? Ichika?
I heard that he was going to
have a special training session
with Laura in Arena 4 today.
Today, I'll be Ichika's specialty coach.
Nice to meet you.
Student council president being a coach?
Ichika-san, what's up with that?
This is uh...
I lost in a match.
Hmm hmm, I think it was for Ichika-kun.
Oh yeah, there's something that
I need your cooperation with.
"Our"?
"Cooperation"?
Time is running out,
so let's get started.
Charlotte-chan and Cecelia-chan
show me the shooter circle float.
Could a shooting-style battle
stance be helpful to Ichika?
Here we go!
Ichika, please pay close attention.
Here I come, Cecilia!
I'm ready!
This is...
They're shooting and
manually controlling their
high-level altitude at the same time.
Not only that, they're doing this
while paying attention to both
evading and targeting, so...
Do you get it?
When'd you get there?!
Ichika!
What are they doing?!
Really!?
You guys alright?
Now it's your turn, Ichika.
Good grief!
Here I come!
O-okay.
This is so different...
Alright, begin firing.
Ichika!
Ichika, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Cecilia, let's continue, please.
I don't feel like it,
but if you insist...
All right, let's do it again!
Are you doing this because the Byakushiki has long range assault now?
Yeah, that's correct.
But actually that's not the only thing.
An important factor in determining
shooting skills is the
ability to breach armor, correct?
But the maximum output of
his charged-particle gun,
which isn't capable of rapid fire,
is more like a sniper rifle.
In other words, he focuses all of his power into one shot.
But it's clear that Ichika does not have good shooting skills.
...you're purposely making him
fight in a close range battle.
That's right. You're pretty sharp.
Man I'm exhausted.
Welcome home!
Shall I prepare dinner?
Or a bath?
Or would you like... Me?
Welcome home!
Would you like me?
Or would you like...
(わたし Watashi= me)
Wa-
Wa- ta-
Wa- ta- shi?
What are you planning?
What?
Since I'm your special coach,
I wanna bond with
you by sleeping and
eating with you.
W-well...
Ta-da!
It's just a swimsuit!
Ichika-kun your reaction was so cute.
Yes! Who is it?
It's me!
I've brought some food for you.
Can I come in?
Houki! No! Sorry.
What are you doing, Ichika?
Oh, I get it!
You don't want her knowing you're messing around.
Ichika, you bastard.
You took this random girl back to your room.
Does your perversion have no bounds?
You should be ashamed of yourself!
Wait, wait! It's a misunderstanding!
I'm sorry, but I'd be pretty mad if you
kill Ichika right now.
Wha-!
It's over!
Your center of gravity is off!
Correct that now!
Y-yes, Ma'am!
Ichika you're very yielding to your seniors aren't you.
Damn it...
Drop your speed.
Concentrate.
Alright!
Okay. I see you picked up speed.
Now try to use Ignition Boost.
What?
Ignition Boost!
Shift to a straight-line maneuver
from the circular orbit
of your Shooter Flow.
Break through the opponent's
barrage all at once
and use the charged-particle
gun at point-blank range!
Just wait a second! I can't
do that all of a sudden...
Now!
O-okay!
Owww...
Remember not to suspend the
Shooter Flow while charging.
Difficult isn't it?
No good. You need to learn how.
Get up and try it again.
Okay.
Ichika, you alright?
Oh what is it?
Do you want some tea?
If you can't eat anything, you
should at least drink some tea.
Thanks, Char...
Anyways, what is that woman up to?
She's got student council work.
Well it's your fault you provoked her in the first place.
But she didn't have to beat
you up this badly though.
I guess I got what I deserved.
I guess I really am weak.
I need to master it as soon as possible.
I think boys who don't give up are cool..
Yeah, I'm often jealous of you.
Ichika-san you can stop by my room if you're feeling bitter.
Hey, wait a second, Cecilia!
Ichika, you should come to my room!
I have playing cards!
Wait! I have playing
cards in my room, too.
How about hanafuda cards, Ichika?
I even have tarot cards in my room!
Go higher, gaze up through the beautiful sky,
takaku motto beautiful sky
Our gaze will make it all the way through
suki tooru manazashi e
mamoritai kagayaki ga kyou mo
The light I want to protect
chikara ni naru yo
becomes my power once again today
naranda kaze ni kimi wo kanjiru
I can feel you in the breeze
sonzai ga ureshii
Your very being makes me happy
shinkokyuu shite miageru sora wa
When I take a deep breath and gaze into the sky
mainichi chigau kao nan da
It looks different every time
doko made mo ikeru ne
We can go anywhere
egaiteku koko kara
We just have to pace it out from here
kinou yori tsuyoi jibun de itai
I want to be stronger than I was yesterday
itsu demo
All the time
takaku motto beautiful sky
Let's go higher into the beautiful sky
suki tooru manazashi ni
Our gaze will make it all the way through
kono shunkan wo yakitsukete iku
Let's burn this moment into our hearts
hikaru motto beautiful sky
Let's bring more light into this beautiful sky
tsubasa goto dakishimete
I'll embrace you and your wings
mamoritai kagayaki ga kyou mo
Since the light we want to protect
chikara wo kureru
gives us our strength today
N-no one is around, right? Good.
Ichika, I like you.
I-I like you, Ichika!
Ichika, will you make miso soup for me?
Ichika nyaa I like you a lot nyaa.
Chi-Chifuyu-san?!
Translucent Chord of Cinderella's Heel
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
Translucent Chord of Cinderella's Heel.